[Music]
hello and welcome to the junkyard love
podcast at what age do we learn how to
have better
conversations at what age should we
learn to have better conversations with
ourselves
[Music]
uh Hoy junkyard lovers it is I Darkwing
Duck the host of the junkyard love
podcast I'm happy you're here today's
episode is a special one it is the last
episode in the original junkyard love
podcast Studio I've changed situations
I've moved scenarios the podcast will
certainly go on things will be business
as usual so to kick off our business as
usual I'm going to give you a
recommendation today's recommendation
before we get going with the episode is
in the form of a 27 minute long YouTube
video it's fantastic you could just
listen to it if you want but there's
lots of cool animations on it as well
it's from the after school uh Channel on
YouTube after space SK L school and it's
called living in survival versus living
in creation Dr Joe dispenza it's great I
really benefited a ton myself um you
know healing from my depression changing
my thought patterns uh not living in the
same lifestyle and and living in the
same downward spiral that I seem to have
been caught in uh Dr Joe despenza helped
me a ton a quick little bio on Joe
despenza he's an international lecturer
researcher corporate consultant author
and educator has been divided to speak
in more than 32 countries on five
continents as a lecturer and educator he
is driven by the conviction that each of
us has the potential for greatness and
unlimited abilities in his easy to
understand encouraging and compassionate
style he has educated thousands of
people detailing how they can rewire
their brains and recondition their
bodies to make lasting changes doesn't
that sound good check out some of this
stuff after school living in survival
versus living in creation Dr Joe
despenza now let's get it Bracken with
the wonderful the charismatic the
friendly the great storytelling the
joyous Connor and shoot
[Music]
yeah I wonder if do you think voicemail
like like with with technology advancing
do you think that voicemail will ever go
away or like phone calls willever will
ever go away I think it's going to
change personally I think uh I mean it's
hard to think of because be like the
Indians trying to think of cell phones
now God just some form of communication
besides smoke signals and writing
letters are like oh [__] that's alien
technology pretty much but I think it'll
probably change somehow like I know Elon
Musk wants to do the uh the chip so then
you can't get away from it you're like
this [__] screening
me I can hear him thinking that he
doesn't want to answer the phone yeah
yeah I mean that's the thing Elon Musk
with the with nurlink he was talking
about um like we're eventually going to
get to the point where we are like
telepathic in a way yeah that's going to
be so weird you can't hide anything it's
all right there it'll get to the point
because then you can't hide your
thoughts once you're chipped and Linked
In I'm I'm afraid that we think that
understand Consciousness more than we do
when we go when we lean into these
directions yeah you ever think that
because
like I don't like we don't really
understand thoughts like like who we are
our identity like what the words we say
out loud does not correlate with the
[__] that's in each of our minds like I
think crazy [__] all day every day all
the time yeah and like if that was my
they're like well that's who Jake is
they'd be like oh [__] yeah cuz you have
those uh uh the pulling of the darkness
I think is what it's called something
like that where like when you're driving
down the road at night and then you're
like I want to Swerve to the right into
these trees and you're like oh [__] no I
don't yeah intrusive thoughts that's
what I call them yeah yeah pulling of
the darkness I like I think it's like
that or something it it's roughly that
the pull of the Void is what it's called
ooh yeah isn't that interesting like I
feel like those when when you first
start experiencing that or maybe like it
comes to your awareness that you have
like weird random thoughts like that
it's kind of a scary thing at first like
like a oh shoot shoot like who who was
that who wait who just thought that yeah
what I don't think those things why
would I think that I don't want to I
don't want to drive over the median and
hit that car face on you know but it
still pops up think's an 87 Honda Civic
that thing's worth its weight and gold
brand new brand new how dare you how
dare you oh dude that's a good movie I
haven't seen that forever what is that
Employee of the Month Employee of the
Month yeah I'm G to add that to the list
to
watch um yeah so I think that nurlink oh
that TV just shut off I think that
nurlink so they did a live demo of it um
a few weeks ago yeah with the pig right
with the pig yeah and I we so we had it
was actually the day that we were
setting up the virtual show okay um and
so we kind of had it playing over in the
corner like not really watching it and
we'd like the three of us occasionally
like glance at it yeah it's the way that
Elon talks about it
is like oh my God like it's hard to even
imagine what it's going to be like so
he's saying that we're going to have
have the ability to like what if you
have the neuralink um chip you're going
to be able to like rewire neural
connections and like so if you have like
injuries like you said it's going to be
able to like heal people's [__] like
broken arms if you have like if you're
blind it's going to be able to help you
form reform new new links in the in the
eye like kind of tell like stem cells
where to go in a sense yeah which is
weird because that would
then would would you do do you think you
would do it from a computer or would it
be this like epigenetic like
uh like your thoughts like you have to
like think like okay imagine it forming
like like do do you think you have to
Eid it with your thoughts like with your
will I mean I think if you use your will
your the mind's pretty powerful I think
you can do stuff with your mind
naturally like if I'm feeling sick I can
like force myself not to get sick be
like oh man I'm feeling like a little
under the weather I know I need to go
home rest and kind of get my body that
bit but then the next time I'm feeling
great where if I'm I hyper fixate on it
it kind of gives you uh
hypochondriac where then you start
making more symptoms and then it's like
a girl having a false pregnancy where
they can put themselves into a pregnancy
by thinking about it and there won't be
she can be a virgin and still get that
don't you think that that stuff should
be investigated more like the fact that
our minds can control like our our
physiology our biology I think so I I
feel like we should I mean because it's
it just it it instantly steps to woowoo
yeah though so so like any scientist is
like I'm not going to ruin my career by
touching that looking into this yeah
uhuh yeah it's going to make me look
like a loon or something and yeah I
think there's a lot of stuff that
medicine should touch on like mushrooms
with the stone date
Theory uh explain the stone DPE Theory
to any listener who has never heard of
it because I love Stone Dae Theory it's
uh basically back in prehistoric times
where monkeys or caveman started eating
mushrooms got really [__] up or stoned
and created language and different uh
forms of chemic
communication yeah like uh it just seems
to make sense right because you know if
we evolve straight from apes like we are
so different than Apes though is the
thing like I we were just talking before
this like we have kind of yeah we're at
the top of the food chain but we've kind
of like got like we're out of the food
chain now like it's like we're just
we're able to affect whatever we need to
on the food chain and we're now this
thing that's outside of it like we're
not just Predators we can if we want to
we could kill all the whales yeah you
know easily they can't come on
land yeah so so that that's the thing is
that's where it gets like like like
religious or spiritual instantly though
our understanding of it
because
how like like like what is a mushroom
then you know like like if we got out of
trees we're monkeys MH however many
years ago what what 200,000 years ago
400 like I'm not quite too sure on the
exact date but yeah yeah I feel like I I
I sound really stupid when I try to go
exact but for BC so yeah but so we we
start walking around and we're [__]
we're trying to survive we get out of
the trees and we start like what turning
over cowp pies we start find like eating
food you know like and eventually like
you just eat a shitload of mushrooms and
it sends you to another planet we're
still physically here like I don't know
if it's like the birth of Consciousness
or if it like just fueled what
Consciousness was already going towards
I think it's proven that uh in pts
people PTSD uh mushrooms
COC cybin uh rebuilds neurop Pathways in
the brain through people with depression
and PTSD and stuff and so it could maybe
link up different neurons and react in
that
way yeah that's crazy though
but it's so it's so weird though because
how does it have the guy I'm like trying
to pour this beer too how do we how do
we have the guidance like what is it
just can we just say nature or biology
is the thing that like
tells okay okay so if we're not using
we're we're monkeys and we're like not
of course we're not like using conscious
thought to be like eat this mushroom and
then like okay form new neural pathway
so we can be the most epic species ever
and we could get all the other animals
it's like what gives it the nudge in
that direction like how does our brain
or whatever it is know to go in the
direction of like intelligence you know
what I mean I think it could have been
like like with the dolphins and puffer
fish just animals like to get high not
like cats and catnip monkeys are
probably just like man have you tried
these Jeff these things are
great look at Jeff go Jeff is super high
and then all it's like been hundreds of
years and they're like oh [__] we are
super sophisticated now like you're
talking I'm Rome has
arisen yeah they're halfway through
being Gladiators before they realize
that we're so intell
yeah it's so fascinating I dude I really
like the stone ape Theory when
I so so for me I feel like I never I
never gave it much thought like was like
what am I what is this why am I here how
did I get these thoughts what are
thoughts like all that just I never I
didn't give it much thought until a
couple years back and then um like
through Joe Rogan and Terence McKenna
and Dennis McKenna and stuff discover
the stone ape Theory and I feel like the
more I listen to it and the more I hear
just like people explain it in different
ways it starts to be like damn it seems
like it makes sense man like what we are
is we started eating a bunch of like
psychedelic substances and they expanded
whatever our Consciousness is if
Consciousness is kind of like the um
let's say leader of evolution or
something for us at least um it started
like just feeding that and amping it up
and we're just tripping [__] balls
flying a rock through space yeah we
seems about right yep we are flying on a
giant space Rock and we forget
that puts everything in perspective I
know I love feeling small yeah it's like
makes you feel big at the same time yeah
it does I'm I'm walking up here I took
this bread and turned it into beer
enjoying it long for the Wild Ride yeah
it's because it's we really are
something different you know humans are
something different because because
we're all the other animals to us anyway
as far as our understanding of them
anyway is they're just like they're
getting comfort so safety it's it's
survival they're still stuck in just
survival they're just trying to eat and
[__] and eat and [__] and we have this I
mean we still just pretty much want to
eat and [__] do yeah but we have this
like way more complicated like we have
this insane pursuit of like
technological advancement and stuff do
you think that we humans are the organic
bootloader of AI as Elon Musk
says yeah I mean also besides Elon Musk
there's other scientists I can't
remember the names right now who also
believe we're like in a in a matrix yeah
like a simulation yeah all part of the
simulation so it could be that we are
the precursors to Ai and once AI comes
online it's supposed to evolve at such a
rapid rate where what took us Millennia
will take them like hours M to evolve to
the next conscious then it's Skynet time
baby all right wait what's Skynet I'm
I'm spacing on Skynet Terminator oh yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah okay right I
just actually so I hadn't ever seen
Terminator until um I mean it was just a
couple months ago I I knew of it though
like it's like you can't not know pretty
much everything about Terminator even if
you haven't watched it but I just
watched it not too long ago um yeah I
don't know man I think
we it seems like we're kind of
approaching that time yeah yeah we're
right on the cusp it it's pretty amazing
within the last 150 years how much
Humanity has changed in their thought
process and with technology going from
Civil War era MH to having airplanes
flying computers in our pockets that are
literally strong 10 times stronger than
the Hubble Space Telescope and now being
connected on a worldwide internet where
before the '90s you had no idea what was
really going on over in Russia or say
Spain or any other country besides
having whatever media Source you have
telling you that whether it be news
radio or paper and now you can just pull
out uh your phone and instantly connect
with somebody via Reddit or messenger or
a forum and know exactly what's going on
at that time you watch it happening on a
live stream even like yeah as it's
happening and it's pretty impressive
that it's bringing us to closer more
together and closer yet giving us this
more distance in dividing us because now
you can throw your own uh perspective on
something and people don't really want
facts they want their own opinion so
they go to Echo Chambers and they will
find something to reinforce their point
of view instead of be able to talk to
somebody like I'm sure there's things me
and you don't agree on somewhere along
some sort of line but the thing is is
you can actually with some people you
can have a good dialogue and it's like
oh I don't want I don't agree with your
point of view but I'm not getting
triggered or right anything and can
actually have a conversation like I
think it was during Roman times you
can't fill a full cup and so any
conversation you go into you should have
an open mind and be willing to change
your mind and Converse because if you go
into a conversation with a full mindset
then you're going in for the sake of
argument instead of
conversation yes dude that was
brilliantly said actually I feel like
that last no I feel like it was because
right now we need those sort of like
thoughts to cuz we're we're such in a
tangle right now I mean we're whether
we're on the cups of something crazy as
a as a species or not like we we are
doing things that we don't realize that
we're doing like so many people are
coming because we're just being like
just camfed with information information
information like we're addicted to
information yeah it's coming at you at
such a fast pace where what's the next
thing this this and this just like 2020
it's always one uping itself so you
never know what's going on but you're
looking for that next instant high it's
like getting a whole bunch of likes on
Facebook or Instagram and getting that
dopamine release yeah instead of going
out and doing things and associating
with people on individual level yeah
it's like a I mean it's kind of like our
our biology has been hacked in such an
intricate Savage [__] way almost I
mean like whether you want to like blame
it on the big corporations or like you
know the the big suit and ties at the
head of all this stuff but or or or not
but like we
are our biolog like dopamine triggers
like the our phone is designed just like
a slot machine like like you you pull
down the thing and it makes a little
noise and it has a little loading screen
and you're just like what's what's Happ
a little heart shows up and you're like
yes little red yeah and it's like but
you know it and it's difficult to do but
I feel like once you start noticing you
you have this awareness
of what's causing it yeah of like like
okay what are my emotions and and why
why am I excited what does it mean to be
excited like well we have
neuroscientists who have proven and and
narrowed these things down it's like
okay it's a it's a brain's neurochemical
release like it's these chemicals like
you can have someone connected to like a
um neonet or something yeah yeah like
have that thing on their head and have
them on their phone and you can
literally watch which synapsis are
firing and not hanging off yeah well
it's just like in the movie industry uh
if you're watching a horror movie look
for the color orange or yellow and
that'll give you a Telltale sign of when
like something's going to happen because
it uh causes stress in humans the color
orange and
yellow uh as a visual reception because
it's like a danger sign and so if you
watch like a horror movie and you see
like yellow lighting kind of that
orangish yellow you know something's
going to pop out soon or something's
going to happen I've watched a whole
bunch of movies uh horror movies after
learning that and I was like oh well
boom this something's going to happen
within the next so much or else if it
doesn't it's just like a you can tell
that's a buildup or suspense right and
then the next scene's probably like when
the murder is actually on screen it's
probably red yeah it's like chasing I
mean if you think of the the like uh
like solar plexus and sacral chakra I
think is yellow and orange as far as
chakras and the energy Setters in our
body mhm I think
that you know you'll see and you can
even see it on Instagram and stuff like
people will post these like this this
chakra yellow is correlated to these
things and it'll show you kind of like
instances in your life or like feelings
that you get her emotions or whatever I
mean it's interesting how much of that
stuff starts to overlap like you know
you see orange and and then it makes you
feel like this anticip anticipatory
feeling um robin's egg blue starts
making it calm down and relax yeah man
it's interesting so what what what's
going to happen when we when we solve
ourselves to such a degree that
we because that's the thing is the the
beauty and Mystery of Life are both
intertwin like not knowing is The Wonder
of life like Wonder is what makes this
so great when we take away all the
Wonder it's kind of hard to Envision
what's on the other side for us well I
think that's one of really good things
about being human is that
you you have the opportunity
to go out and pursue things that you
really like and that you love and not
knowing about it and then when you dive
into a subject you get really passionate
about and it just gives you the dopamine
and serotonin that the body craves and
it you can really uh like I said
hyperfixate on something and learn about
it yeah when it kind of levels you up
too yeah yeah it's it's like the more
like the more knowledge you it's hard to
see and it's hard to quantify because in
the middle of learning it you're you're
not thinking of your life as like on
this big timeline but good way to kind
of disassociate and disconnect yeah yeah
yeah oh it's so interesting it's crazy
that I don't know man it does seem like
we're speeding up with everything
everything like like mors law everything
is going so much faster but sometimes I
just fear that we're going in the
direction
that I I fear that we haven't figured
out exactly what we are or what we're
trying to do before we have sped in this
direction like look at um uh Lex
Friedman was talking with with Joe Rogan
um on a podcast a couple days ago and
he's basically talking about bees like
to the individual bee I don't think that
they have a comprehension that they're
like in a hive on a
world uh like making honey like like
what like what what is the bee doing
like everything they're doing
microscopically throughout the day yeah
but like what are they ultimately doing
they're making honey that's what bees do
um but like what are humans doing like
what we're making a
ey precursor to that just building up
refining the wheel and refining it and
refining it till we pretty much end up
like Wall-E in the Wally World just yeah
in these sweet chairs living life eating
oh my god that's way sooner than we
think I think oh yeah already has the
crispy cream sandwiches fried chicken
sandwiches life is good dude I forgot
about those until right now have you had
them yet no not yet sadly I I want to
try it I think it'd be [__] delicious
chicken waffles pretty much on a
sandwich yeah it's funny that I uh so we
eat like I always thought the chicken
and waffles was a weird combo and then
someone's like bro you eat bacon in the
morning I'm like bacon bacon and a
pancakes or making bacon pancakes Bing
bacon pancakes panc first you make bacon
then you make a pancake
bless it yeah I
uh man it's interesting because I
have I mean I I I watch too much YouTube
that's for sure the problem but I have I
just have intuitions and feelings and I
really I don't I don't know I can't
fully explain it but I feel like
whatever the singularity is or whatever
they thought that it was going to be it
will happen while you you and I are
alive I really feel like that I can
definitely see that coming to rition
yeah that's probably going to be [__]
tomorrow or or something I'd be fine
with it I'd be chill with it way call me
home Jesus what if okay what if
humans okay I always thought of like a
like so now we have this like rush like
people like Elon and stuff like trying
to get off the planet right so what if
we see what if what we're trying to do
is we are just part of biology like we
separate to make civilization work we
separate everything and we call it like
like beer bottle glass table so it makes
sense and we could have culture but
compartmentalized yeah but but at the
root of everything if you didn't know
the labels they are just where this is a
one this is one happening from the
beginning of time um and and we are you
could say we are Earth or we are biology
or we are I don't know I mean it gets
hippie dippy quick but like what if our
goal is to kind of like get some seeds
out like before the Earth does something
crazy itself what if like we are the
seeds that's uh that's actually a Theory
it's
on can't remember I watched it on a kste
it's a German uh educational thing on
YouTube really cool they put it into
really bite-sized information and they
animate it with like little birds and
stuff and it talks about each step
of uh civilizations coming through and
we're right below where the next step
would be to get as much energy as we can
harness which would be to create like a
level three Society or something like
that where you harvest the energy
straight from the Sun where I think they
had talked about it a while back where
some other civilization
possibly quote unquote was out in a
different star system and it looked it
just by the way it was blocking the sun
which could be a moon could be asteroid
you never know but uh it just takes all
the radiation energy from that and feeds
it straight to the
planet and then you have unlimited
energy source from that way and then
once you get to start ship travel either
you have to go War of the World War of
the Worlds where you have to harvest
plants for water Nutri nutrients and
everything
else and we haven't seen any other
civilizations out there aliens and stuff
to see where the cap is but there's a a
step
where either everything goes good and
and all kind of goes together or else it
collaps and the whole species dies off I
can pull it up and send it to you it's a
pretty cool L yeah that sounds awesome I
feel like I would love to follow that
channel what was it called one more time
uh
kste k e r z g s t e d I think isn't it
so cool so even even that like think
about how like you're able to learn that
theory or even like that it exists and
you're able to get it in a bite size
like 8 minute video or something you
know rather than you know think about 15
50 years ago 100 years ago like it's
like if you don't know the right people
who have the right books on hand you
don't get to ever know that information
no travel like across the country to get
there well I talk about um you know
Enlightenment for example you know like
I I am I heavily study like meditation
and these things and the amount of
information I know compared to what I
would have been able to know even 30
years ago yeah like I I can just sit and
watch YouTube video like so so people
like Sam Harris like he has spent time
um being being in like the the Tibetan
mountains or whatever um uh Tibetan
mountains might be a very arrogant thing
to say I'm not sure or something like
that so he he's like he's met the
Masters like he's he's had conversations
with enlightened Masters he's got done
the firsthand experience like meditated
silent Retreats for six months like
those sort of things well now he comes
back and makes an app that teaches
people all over the world how to do
basically because he's like okay what am
I getting towards I'm getting towards
this final goal you know Enlightenment
or leaning towards it or the
understanding of your own Consciousness
and your own um um whatever we call Self
yeah
but the the fact that I I'm a [__]
28-year-old DJ from Kelo Washington and
I'm able to like massively learn a lot
of the same things that he spent years
and years learning and then 30 years
before that yeah it was even you'd have
to devote your entire life to even get
like what I am able to learn in one day
of just like hardcore like studying his
app in his lectures and his
conversations with other like um like
Buddhist monks and stuff Jus and
everything yeah like what I'm able to
learn one day
is 40 Years of of of work for a lot of
people you know what I mean like again
you got to put in the time with
meditation because you have so much
stuff to unwind but yeah it's so clear
that we
are so okay so what about this
Conor
time do you think that
time might be because that's what's
Happening Here is time is getting less
and less like
[Music]
important like like do you think our
next step when we like take the next big
jump are we going to somehow it's hard
to conceptualize because our reality is
formed by our five senses and time and
gravity and those sort of things but
what if
we what if we like our intelligence has
just not figured out how to like get
over the evolutionary EV evolutionary
step of time I mean time is kind of like
a concept in my mind uh when just say
like if you're really happy and you're
hanging out with friends time goes by
really quick uh and so it's all relative
to what's going on around you and like
when you're young you're wanting to be
old sooner than you can mhm but then
when you're old you're like man I wish I
have just slowed down a little bit when
I was a kid and spent more time doing
this and this cuz I could have gone out
and played with my friends at this time
M up at the Transformer box or the
corner of the street go play some
baseball or skateboard around and do
kids stuff like poops bags of poop on
fire people's uh porches you know just
day all day just good things uh
depending on who your neighbor is but I
think that
people need to just realize
what's important to them and then they
can more so focus on it and then I think
when you when you cherish something and
you really focus on it time goes by it
seems like at the right pace you're not
like you enjoy it so it goes by quick
but you're enjoying every moment of it
and the little things are making it
count so then you create the memories
which makes it seem
longer yeah that's true
because yeah when you're it seems like
yeah the right thing to do is almost
like this you're kind of just not caring
or unaware of time like it's not really
that it slows down as bopping through
things yeah it just is you're just doing
the thing and time happens to be through
the motions yeah that's so interesting I
wonder going to work at somewhere and
every day is the same thing then you
can't wait to get off work and the
weekends never seem long yeah Northwest
Hardwoods yeah Lumber Mills yeah oh yeah
I don't miss that job um
yeah but yeah dude I yeah that's so
interesting I wonder if well
because so when it comes so Einstein's
theory relativity yeah
so I'm I'm wondering if we're like on
the edge of a big physics breakthrough
but we're going to learn that it's not
so
much
like okay okay so so quantum physics
okay we [__] we zoom in we keep
zooming in like like what like physical
reality but just like keep zooming in
like we keep zooming in and we keep just
finding more stuff the better macro yeah
and you keep zooming out and the
universe keeps expanding just like the
Grand Theft Auto like when you're
playing Grand Theft Auto and you
discover more of the map it just keeps
highlighting itself so far every time we
zoom out it just keeps getting bigger
and every time we zoom in it just like
gets we're okay it's deeper and deeper
there's more stuff here there's more
stuff here there's more stuff here
everything big is everything small and
everything small is everything big mhh
so what if what
if here here's a new physics gesture
what if neither of those are the correct
way I don't know where we could go from
there but it's like instead of zooming
in or zooming out and advancing our
technology to get farther or look more
in depth like what if it's somehow
neither I don't know where I'm going
with that really but it's just like be
going towards like more energy conscious
way instead of looking at a physical
world looking at like an energetic world
like doing chakras and stuff and yeah
trying to look Inward and using the
energy CU I mean we're just electrical
beings in a meat
suit
essentially uh and so it could be
something
electrical where then it would go back
to like we had previous previously
discuss about being a precursor to Ai
and just being biomechanical robots so
I hope we don't accidentally create the
wrong AI I feel like we're we're dumb
and we're going to make the wrong AI oh
we already have uh once some well that
too uh got zucked on a couple of my
Facebook posts um but
the I can't remember who made it but
there was a person who made an AI put it
on like 4chan or something like that and
within 24 hours it became Like A
Nazi uh praised Nazi person because it
would take stuff that people are posting
and reading and posting on it and then
people just start posting a lot of bad
stuff into it and so it just became this
Super Hyper violent uh
nazist uh entity bro that is literally
the best example of what's actually
already [__] happening right now on
social media pretty much have you
watched uh the social Dilemma on Netflix
I have not yet it's rather new you'll
you'll definitely enjoy it it kind of
talks about there's basically a couple
AIS in place for like Facebook Twitter
like like
um definitely listeners have to watch
this documentary I've already think I
recommended it like three times already
just since this came out but um
basically I got the feeling that there's
AIS in place that even the people at the
heads of these company they don't really
know what it's doing they're just like
it's you know it's it's it's getting
more viewers online but like what does
it doing how is it getting more viewers
onl how is it learning to get these I
mean it's bringing us more online and
it's bringing us so like okay so say the
goal is to AI here you here is the task
that I'm assigning you as a human who
has who has developed this algorithm
your task AI is to get users on the
platform longer or keep them on the
platform
longer it's going to do that in ways
that we don't understand and it's going
to do that in ways that
we I mean it may almost have its own
creative nature in way be reading us as
animals and so what what keeps him
online is uh do like like what if what
if the AI is affecting human behavior in
such a way that it is like very subtly
very inadvertently that to where we
can't like our egos are protecting us
from even like seeing what we're doing
with it that it's basically like doing
its task it's keeping the humans online
for as much as it can but what if it in
the long run it's like
creating virtual reality itself with
these AIS so basically okay human I'm AI
you said the goal is to keep people
online get them in the virtual world for
as long as possible I'm going to do that
in ways that you can't even imagine and
so it's kind of going to affect human
behavior and like maybe it's like
somehow nudging certain like smart
people in certain ways with their
emotions cuz we are biological creatures
and just small sub of cues like could be
a color like it it could be looking like
a white screen could be like looking at
a white screen on the back of your
Facebook like the background of it but
it could be putting uh like little hints
of orange in certain ones but then
you're like uh I don't like this post
because you're brain's reading it as
like you can't see it being orange
because it looks all white but there's
little Hues like just a shade M and so
it' be like I don't like this post and
then connect it to the person they like
oh well this so and so is who posts this
not even like really thinking because
it's just a face picture name in the
post and then somebody else who it wants
you to associate more with could have
like blue or something like that and be
like oh well this and then it could
trigger like different uh political
mindsets like oh well this is I'm I it
relaxes me when I see this stuff and so
I'm associating more with it and
agreeing more with this and kind of
trains you in an animalistic sense to go
along with whatever
it's uh Forte or not Forte but it's
prerogative is yeah it's multiple choice
it's crazy because as we're talking
about it it's like not it doesn't even
feel like a theory it literally feels
like we're kind of just shittily
explaining exactly how it
is FBI open up hey don't tell people
yeah dude well I mean that's the thing
is it could happen right under our noses
because you know the ego
what we are like what we identify as
like we only kind of take credit for the
good stuff yeah like the other stuff or
like we didn't do that or we didn't um
like I don't think that or you know like
like like people can be virtue signaling
without realizing their virtue signaling
people can be like protecting their own
self from Pain without realizing that's
what they're doing they're like what are
you do dude I'm just arguing with this
person I'm just saying it's because it's
wrong and blah blah and they get going
on their thing but where we are we got
to remember we're we're creatures man
we're the thing after apes and we have
emotions and our emotions are you know
controlled by all these like chemicals
in our body yeah and those are some
pretty crazy things in themselves like
being able to have the different
emotions like you can't have happy
without sad and vice versa it's dark
without light you can't appreciate being
happy without having periods of being
sad yeah if you're happy all the time
you would be like this is what is normal
yeah it's normal this is life yeah
there' be nothing to contra conted to
yeah that's why that's why you know
balance is so important too like in so
many ways cuz it literally is like dude
balance creates what you are it does it
does it really does and you have to be
able to disassociate from things and
look like you said look inside meditate
however it might be some people with you
I'm guessing you take time to yourself
and meditate other people go out in the
woods and go hunting MH MH as their form
of retreat and get to spend the time
alone in that sense being in nature or
uh going mountain biking or running and
things like that what do you think okay
to if someone was listening right now
and they would just and and say they say
they're someone who's on their phone all
the time but they're just they like
being on their phone they have a
business they're whatever like they're
they're like yeah I know I should
probably be on my phone less but it's
whatever it's not controlling my
thoughts I would know right yeah and
when you say things like meditation
going out in nature um if they say what
what it so their initial reaction is
those are those are just things that I'm
not interested in those are not my
interests my interest is talking to my
friends on my phone my interests are
playing my video games for 18 hours a
day like what whatever it is and I'm not
I'm not hating on anybody like live your
life bro I'm notes different folks yeah
uh but I'm just saying like how do
we how do we okay cuz I feel like me
four years ago mhm I would say that's
just not what I'm interested in yeah
completely different person you were
really into Spartan races and yeah yeah
yeah do still did Spartan races yeah
they're not around right
now I remember seeing you down in clama
with a weighted vest climbing up a
really big steep Sand Hill right the
heat ahead of me I was like dang Jake's
going for it bro yeah I was like well so
I've done I've done quite a few of those
um and I love them and they're really
enjoyable i' I've never tried to like
win because the people who win are
[__]
Savages like they're literally people
who travel around the world to race
Spartan races and that's their whole
life and I just don't have the time to
compete with that but so I would just
like try to challenge myself and i' done
quite a few so wait this you know yeah
you should always challenge yourself in
any aspect of life uh you should never
settle you should always like pursue the
next thing uh never stop learning never
stop going when you slow down I mean
we're animals when you slow down and
stuff the body starts realizing it you
have to things motion tend to stay in
you see people who you see old people
who are just Cy and hory and stuff but
they have a passion or hatred driving
them every day to wake up screw the
neighbor kids standing on my yard I'm
going to go out there I'm going to
maintain it get it all crisp and cut and
they could be like 95 years old sharp as
attack Y and you see people who will sit
at home just kind of sit in the couch
grow roots in the floor and vegetate
then their mental capacity really starts
going down downhill mhm with Dementia or
other ways that's just how I've kind of
personally seen it yeah cuz we are what
we feed like like just like when it
comes to like the chakras I mean you
like if you feed your you know three
lower ones rather than your four upper
ones you know like when you when you
just do what safe I mean we we came from
we came from being creatures that like
obviously want survival want safety like
it's safe in this cave so stay in this
cave but then there's also this other
side that's like but there could be more
than just this cave there could be world
yeah uh no it's it's a pretty pretty
wild thing to kind of think
about we have a call to Adventure within
us yeah it's much
needed a Wonder sense of wonder lust
wonderlust have you seen that movie
wonderlust no oh man it's so okay so it
has Paul red and Jennifer Anderson
actually it's like she so beautiful
she's she's wonderfully beautiful she
might be a [__] robot I think she's
just too pretty same with uh
Reeves he can be whatever he wants to be
he's a good person he's he's he's
awesome dude I I feel like he's so dope
I so for one I did hear that the Matrix
4 is coming out yeah and John Wick for
are also coming like I think that I
heard they're coming the same day or
something like he's talking about
Universe too oh what however he
intertwines those is going to be the
coolest thing I've ever seen in my whole
life I think think he'll be cuz somebody
had an interview with K Reeves recently
he he seems like a really interesting
person I'd love to love to meet sometime
yeah have a beer with that guy that'd be
great yeah talk about motorcycles uh
that's what he's all about is riding
motorcycle he dude could sack some
bodies I'm sure I've seen him training
for John Wick and he's does he do his
own stunts on everything I think so I
think he does he probably does he seems
like the guy would cuz he did all the
training for like the running arms and
stuff training through
and it's impressive like his shots are
dead on great uh great cardio gu's just
a impressive human yeah respect for him
yeah yeah I would love to I I like his
his image is very like clean too I feel
like he's always like anything you ever
hear is just like he's a sweet guy he's
always polite um he doesn't really go
like out of his way like there is
interviews of him you know but he
doesn't like go out of his way for
publicity and stuff he he just he just
he just does his work you know that's
what it seems like yeah he seems really
down to earth uh cuz he rides I think
like commercial he's not like one of the
guys who has to have a private jet and
that's be all extra bougie he's just
like oh this is me just walking on
riding the subway just being a human
well you got to do you know you got to
we get used to [__] we get used to you
know our comfort levels and and I feel
like so many people just keep leveling
up I'm sure it'd be difficult and I'm
sure I would if given money
opportunities I'm sure that I would want
to level up to you know yeah but I feel
like it's uh you know humbling yourself
or like choosing to stay out of like a
humble level of certain certain things
you know kind of a level of godliness
right there yeah like money greed
changes people makes them less
empathetic it's been proven
scientifically uh like high up CEOs
justu that part off of yeah it's all
business uh I mean some people know but
majority kind of seems like that I'm not
a conspiracy theorist but you just seem
crazy till is
proven right hey dude I'll be conspiracy
theorist all day man I don't care you
know it's funny Eric Weinstein talks
about conspiracy theories he's like you
know pretty much anything that's like
proven to be untrue or Unwound like
there has to be a crazy person at the
beginning saying like hey this [__] is
crazy yeah the world's round man yeah we
have to have we we have to have room for
conspiracy we do we have to CU we're
that's what we're doing here we're
trying to like what is that thing within
us where we're trying to constantly
understand what this really is like
that's I mean you have to be able to
question your own reality and question
like Bad actors and and especially you
just said like CEOs and like big high up
people they're able to shut off their
Humanity like this is the [__] The
Vampire Diaries and they can just turn
it off like a switch like we've got to
be able to see what what's up with that
because they're just looking out for
them when the heart of human is looking
out for like the whole species yeah all
for one Musketeers kind of yeah they
uh they had this really good uh I was
really impressed with it it was a want
to say it was a documentary on society
but instead of using people they used
rats and they had I want to say from
like the 70s they had this big compound
as big as your house dedicated to just
rats they had like 150 different rooms
for each rat and it was supposed to be
the perfect
Society uh they changed out the bedding
every day everything uh and they put
rats in there to breed as a colony and
to see what would happen if they had no
worries about food or housing or
cleanliness oh right right and it got up
to I think like 15,000 rats or something
like that I can't remember exact number
I'm not going to say verbatim it was
exactly
14623 yeah but it got up to a certain
point where then they started attacking
each other and killing each other and it
uh went down it had a big population
boom and then shrank and then after it
shrank and kind of stabilized they had
the the clean ones I think or the
unblemished or something like that rats
who lived in a different section of the
whole
colony and they had no scratch marks on
them and everything and all the other
ones uh there would be several open h
holes for Open Homes where they could
stay and there' be food in it but they
would all bundle up like 150 Rats on one
giant group per place I can't remember
what the experiment was called it's a
really interesting uh that sounds fasc
documentary I'd highly recommend it I
can I can't remember what it was called
but Jamie pull up rat documentary rat
documentary yeah need a Jamie yeah I
want to say it was during like the 70s
when they did it and it was a huge
compound like so what ises it what does
that tell us then I mean I mean cuz that
could I mean know so what does it tell
us about rats but what does that tell us
about I mean even humans yeah Society
like is it it so is beauty a thing there
or is it were the rats that weren't
scratched up and stuff were they just
maybe like more logical like like in my
head I'm kind of thinking like the ones
that weren't scratched up maybe they
were like the the monk like among the
rats that were like this is nonsensical
sensible we need to you know yeah and
they weren't all uh they didn't cram it
either it was it wasn't as highly packed
in the other houses or I say houses but
whatever the rats were in uh there it
was a lot fewer and they had a lot more
open area but all the other ones were
all scratched up and stuff from uh
fighting and so it it could be a lot of
different things uh I hate using a
because it's a filler word I say like
very often my
friend it's just those dang speech
patterns
the we don't know what we're going to
think until we think it man I don't know
what I'm gonna say next I'm just I just
blurt it out usually I'm yeah that's
that's the beauty of a podcast is it's
like like you don't know what you're
gonna [__] say man yeah you're just
gonna say it it's all right get a whole
bunch of hate mail after this be like
man Conor Conor's getting canell yeah
Conor's canceled he's G all these all
the scarred up rats are gonna [__]
send you hate mail can't believe you're
talking bad about rats I'll have you
know I grew up in the scar section yeah
thank you it's
struggling it's been so difficult for me
and my family in this rat house yeah
that's so interesting though I want okay
so what do you think do you think it was
more of like a you think Beauty had a
had a thing in it like is that I think
it did I think it did have a little bit
but I also think
that misery loves company is a really
popular saying and it's true it's
completely 100% true misery does love
company when you're when you're
miserable you like to be around people
who are also miserable you you listen to
sad music you kind of disassociate from
people you isolate instead of like doing
things that make you happy like running
getting exercise healthy body healthy
mind and I think that in that uh rodent
Society know people don't really like
saying rat of rodents but flora fauna
but I think that they kind of bonded
together in a mutual uh Mutual setting
where
they just didn't associate with the
other class I think it kind of made a
different hierarchy in the Society of
rodents yeah man that's so weird isn't
it weird to think too you know just like
humans
like I guess we we okay we see rats we
just think of rats and like okay they're
the same species or type of rat like we
can put Rats from Zimbabwe we can put
Rats from Australia we can put Rats from
America we can put Rats from New Zealand
and just put them all in their rats and
so they'll learn how to coincide but I
feel like they they would it they'd
probably fight they'd probably cuz if
you put like two if you put um two
different fire ant colonies together and
you mix them dump them on top of each
other they'll kill each other yeah but
also some other ants will you can take
an ant from France and ant from other
place and you put them together and
they're instantly perfectly fine
yeah oh man it's so interesting I wonder
which like what what causes that what's
so and that's the other thing is we're
always trying to understand things only
up we can only understand things up to
our knowledge and we're also trying to
understand things as it compares to
humans yeah like where you know like
what does it how does it rep
uh B on how does it affect me in a way
like how does it how can this benefit me
or how does it's like the African gra
her is one of the only other animals
that has been able to answer a or ask a
self identifying question what was it
what color am
I that would almost be that's almost
like an AI talking right yeah it it was
uh in the 60s or 7s you got a big old
spider there
buddy he's like you guys are talking
about
ants that was not very Buddhist like no
but [__] that spider
bro I get I get a good amount of spiders
in here yeah keeps me on my to you know
it's actually cool because I'm someone
who used to be afraid of spiders um not
in like a Screech like a girl but I'm
just like I'm not the guy to kill the
spider um I'm not going to get the
napkin I'm like I I like my [__] the
Almond part of my brain the [__]
flight brain yeah it just gets turned on
like it I used to I used to actually
like like feel my heart rate getting
faster when there's a spider but then I
actually over the last few years I
started like literally just like sitting
with it like okay yeah that's a spider
like what if it bites me I'm in trouble
well I mean a lot of the I mean we do
have deadly spiders up here in the
Pacific Northwest black widows yeah um
but I feel like allowing just the seeing
a spider to like let my fight ORF flight
response turn on like that started to
piss me off I was like dude what I'm not
going to let a little spider who likely
is not going to hurt me like I mean for
the most part even if I see him in my
house I could probably just walk away
and i' probably never see him again he
might crawl in my face in my mouth when
I'm sleeping I don't know know but all
you're doing is making spider stronger
man it's scientifically proven what when
you kill a spider it makes him stronger
yeah because uh any spider you kill
makes the ones who hide who hid better
more likely to breed oh so you're just
strengthening up the spider species I
[__] up yep I'm sorry bro sorry super
spiders now yeah they're just coming out
the
walls yeah is it okay if I do my bang
energy Vapes bro Absolutely I'll day do
your thing I don't mind at all I would
normally um I'm taking a a smoke break
right now but I would normally uh
normally join you with with the smokes
do you smoke weed no I can't right now
no if I get C pee and dirty it's goes on
a federal background for me I'll be
screwed because if I uh if I pee dirty I
get my federal license as a merchant
maner credential uh revoked for drug
abuse and then it comes back if I want
to buy like a house later or anything
like that that hey you lost a federal
license for drug abuse that's so I mean
I get it you gotta play the game I
suppose but that is a little silly I
mean yeah so but we're I feel like in
the next couple years I mean there's I
think four or five new States right now
that are like uh proposing to legalize
marijuana well I'm all for I I hand
sound any day would rather smoke a bowl
at the end of the night than to drink uh
I'll have a beer and stuff but like if I
had the option I'd rather smoke a bowl
or smoke a joint M instead of drinking
cuz then you don't feel hung over the
next day you can enjoy a joint blow down
the river and when you wake up I was
talking with one of my good buddies
about this when we're doing concrete
like man I hate this job I'm breaking my
body down get chewed out by all these
dudes
who just they hate your wife and they
take it out on you yeah exactly and it's
like you know you go home you smoke a
bowl and you're like man this job ain't
too bad that's exactly what it is that's
exactly what it is there's something
about it I yeah cuz I um I I'm in the
same boat I would I would prefer to
smoke weed too um it's like I think it
it does make you appreciate what's going
it makes you okay with hanging out with
yourself which is really a huge thing
you know I mean I think probably a lot
of people have discovered that during
this quarantine is like because a lot of
people have been smoking more they
probably realize like dude hanging out
with myself like you know as long as you
don't get too blitzed like reading a
book or like listening to like an
informative podcast I learn like we were
talking about ADHD before like learning
learning the way you learn man me if I
have a subject I'm interested in and I
like take a bong rip and sit down like
I'll be just [__] transfixed for a
few hours I'll be writing notes I'm just
I'm just so much more in depth do the
same thing watch documentaries I just
yeah take it all in I just vegetate and
I watch M if I when I was working for
the city de Mo they I won't like that I
say this but I would wake up in the
morning smokeable it' be either sunny in
the morning or raining and Rain rainy
days would be like oh man it's raining
kind of crappy out and I would just
stand outside be like man this is kind
of relaxing hearing the rank go by
smelling the Petra cor and just enjoying
like the moments as it comes to you I
think this but overall I think this
quarantine has been 50/50 for people I
think it's been healthy for people where
they can go find their creative outlets
and do things that really uh benefit
them in whichever manner it is whether
it's starting a business or even though
it's not really the proper time to
probably start a business but they can
find faucets of life to really Channel
out of and then I think of the yin to
the Yang the light in the dark uh some
people get stuck in their minds get
really bad depression because they're
not some people are really sociable
introverts and uh
extroverts and they're just quarantined
away from everybody they see so then
they get in the deep depression and just
eats away from them on the inside and
then they sometimes put a mask over and
try hiding it instead of like coming
forth and communicating with people in
different matters whether it be Xbox
like trying to game with people or any
manner that they can yeah no I dude I
totally agree I mean I that's why at the
beginning of this quarantine I was I'm a
I'm I'm actually a very my natural state
I'm very introverted I I
have you know I I have like like when
I'm not feeling like my anxieties and
and those sort of things when I'm on top
of my game I have my exterior um
extrovert function functions are
sharpened I from just from like
childhood and basically after like being
thrown into the world as a teenager and
have have to work and stuff like find
who you are yeah so I was able to like
I'm good at people I'm good at
interacting with people but my my
favorite state is by myself I love to
hang out by myself you know I'm my
favorite person yeah dude I like myself
and that's a nice thing to say because
some people you know that's that I think
everybody should try to get there you
know a lot of people don't like
themselves and I didn't like myself for
a long time and now you know I like
hanging out myself I like and and weed
[__] helped with that man like just
being able to like you know when I'm
hanging out down here and I do something
dorky where I'm dancing or I'm singing
or whatever it is like tune to a little
Taylor Swift to a little Taylor a lot of
Taylor Swift man she's her and Kanye I
love Kanye all the way through I'm all
I'm all bored Kanye he's been going
crazy lately I love it I mean crazy
lately and I don't mean that as an
insult when I say I I feel like like I
call myself crazy like I'm a crazy
person I I'm I'm nut you're saying
unless you realize your own craziness
yeah dude I I want to be crazy that's
how I feel I don't want to I don't want
to be like everybody else that's what a
world yeah I ain't like that but I dude
weed weed is super helpful I mean so
many people so think about how many
people on a day-to-day basis like you go
to your prescription eye doctor checkup
and while you're sitting there in that
waiting room there's older people next
to you and they're on multiple
medications that the government has
approved and said these are safe but 6
months of FAA yeah and it's like oh
there's no long-term effects of this
yeah see that's the thing it's like
we're so um we we just demonized weird
[__] like weed can be pretty crazy for
people like you know if you have no
familiarity with that sort of thing and
you take like a giant rip of weed it's
going to send you to the rocket to to
the moon on a rocket you know but I
think that different people's minds work
differently like I so when I was on
depression medication in there holy
mother of [__] dude I hated it so much
it feel so bad yeah see so same thing
like so I think like faster paced people
I work well with weed but so I was
thinking like okay like I take like a a
little rip and then an hour later um if
I'm driving like I I don't like to smoke
and drive very often um but I'm just
saying like I I remember thinking like
when I had started smoking weed more
over the last couple years I remember
thinking like after you know it been a
couple hours or whatever driving I'm
like dude yeah like I still have like a
little bit of of the feeling of of weed
um like in in my Consciousness but
compared to when I was driving on
depression medication man I literally
felt like I had to pull over like I felt
so unlike myself like I couldn't have
conversations for the first few weeks
like I remember it was like the fourth
day or something and um cuz like
sometimes when I'm not sharpened on that
extroverted function I get Social
Anxiety a lot of people do and I
remember getting a freaking haircut um
from someone who's my friend like she's
really awesome I just I can [__]
with her I could I literally could have
told her like I'm on this on this
depression medication that's why I'm you
think of it like kind of oh well he's on
this and yeah like I don't want to tell
people and so that's the thing is I
remember um I wasn't my normal self like
it was like I had I had been on the
medication for a few days maybe a few
weeks or something and uh she was like
talking and then she like she had
commented she's like are you okay like
what's what's going on and I remembered
just like the fear over I was like oh my
God am I acting weird like I don't know
how to act who am like I just had this
terrible feeling and dude I I just don't
understand why is one thing just cuz one
dude has decided one [__] Reagan or
whoever the [__] it was demonized these
these drugs and said these are good
these are bad and there's people filling
their pockets with these prescription
drugs there's people driving around who
take a a Xanax every morning or there's
people um who the same situation you're
in you're in the waiting room at the
dentist and maybe the person who's
checking you in who works there and she
takes Zoloft every morning or she takes
whatever where and we're getting to
different states of Consciousness so we
can deal with pain or deal with trauma
or deal with anxious feelings these
sorts of things I don't understand why
like one is so much worse than the other
I mean I listen I I don't want I don't
want to I don't want to be around a ton
of people who are stoned out of their
mind driving forklifts like I get it
yeah's danger thing but I I think that
at the end of the day though when you're
like I got like the 3-day weekend I
can have a barbecue if I burn a couple
bir bur no big deal catching up on some
like Rick and Morty or
whatever but yeah like it's the same
with like drinking at work like you're
not going to catch me drinking at work
or smoking at work right uh but I think
a lot of that stuff needs to be
normalized we've had this we've been
doing uh marijuana crops for centuries
since Roman times where they built roads
with hemp that are still today Ben
Franklin his diary talks about growing
crops stronger and stronger just a good
Weed Farmer uh and then you take that
all away people it's I'm not going to
say it's part
ofver physiology but it's it's ingrained
our system for so long uh I think that's
around the time they made weed illegal
because it was making all our women
leave for black men with reer Madness
you're going to lose your wife to a
black guy all this stuff it's like no
you're probably a piece of [__] who just
didn't pay attention to your wife yeah
what like give her a little attention
every once in a while yeah dude yeah
it's like we we point the finger at the
wrong parts of things for sure it's
always easier pointing the finger away
from you yeah that's true yeah it is
easy it easy it's easy to blame I mean
if I mean I know where we are heading in
the direction I mean with with Sil cybin
being um used for for um etsd color yeah
dude they uh Maps so so I listen to Tim
Ferris um and and he's always kind of
keeping updates on on all that stuff
dude and they're making also MDMA
assisted therapy they're making
breakthroughs bro like they're like it's
like it's like certain studies or like
50% of the people are better within this
amount of time some of them are like 80%
of the people are better a year later
it's literally it blows all these other
like anti-depressants and all these
other things blows them out of the
[__] water yeah and you don't have
all those negative side effects either
you're not having anal bleeding or
anything like that you're just anal
seepage anal seepage that's the worst
yeah dude I yeah I remember had [__]
Kool-Aid coming out of my eyes it was
just it was the worst the side effects
on those damn things yeah like I mean I
was on quite a few myself last year and
that sucked like just all the side
effects and I was like I don't feel like
myself it's
just after that like I knew I was
depressing stuff like heavily and what
worked best for me was I went to one of
my really good friends I think that
every person in their friend group
everybody has like five core friends
pretty much and every friend is a
different Niche for life you can take
the same question to each friend and get
a different answer and you're going to
pick the answer that works best for you
they'll all give you based off their
life experiences this is what you should
do this is what you should do one friend
is like no come with me drink another
friends like the one for me uh best
friend I've known him since kindergarten
uh when I was really down uh went up to
his place he doesn't drink or anything
he had beer in his fridge he's like if
you want a beer it's there and me and
him just sat there played guitar I'm not
good at guitar or any instruments really
but we I just kind of sat there dled
away talked and went trade that for the
life of me and I found that's kind of
what helped me through those times yeah
that that's a therapy right there yeah
like just being able to associate with
people who you connect with who you can
I think a lot of people nowadays have
this hard time opening up to people and
having people you can actually open up
to and talk
to in a
completely uh neutral setting MH where
you're not like oh well I have these
other two people around can't really
talk about this right now or so and so
and I want to stay cool I want I'm
losing my mind or something yeah and
having that level of trust like oh I can
actually trust this person to confine in
and uh give me their best point of view
and then reflect on it it may not be
like the point of view you want to hear
but it'll be a point of view that
sometimes you need to hear yeah yeah
dude that's an
important I mean we we I just love the
the holistic approach to everything like
especially when it comes to our mental
health like you know before you go get
on anti-depressive like you know maybe
like like have you tried reaching out to
friends like have you tried to step out
of your comfort zone in certain levels
like you know I'm sure you know there
might have been a time for you where
you're like you know what sounds good
right now you know what feels good right
now cuz I'm sad I'm not feeling too
great I'm feeling down on myself like
just going to [__] have a drink by
myself and play some video games oh man
that used to be uh that used to be my
go-to whenever I was depressed a long
time ago I would go out in the woods by
myself I'd get a bottle and I'd drink it
yeah did that help for you or that
didn't uh internal a lot okay I internal
that's just like my psychology is I used
to internalize a lot and uh just kind of
I wouldn't Express anything to anybody
I'd just be like hey I'm I'm going
camping this weekend and then I would
just kind of leave it as at and they be
like oh cool where at I'm like oh I'm
just going somewhere just kind of leave
it vaguely then I just dip off in the
woods unbeknown everybody else and i'
just hang out by myself and drink my
sorrows away and now I'm like well
that's definitely an unhealthy that's
meis yeah yeah see we were talking about
I had my friend uh Brian Andrew on a
couple nights ago and we were talking
about just just those those different
things that we do like our defaults like
what I I used to do like I was like had
terrible anxiety and was like incredibly
depressed and had like just just miles
of self-hate for so long like and my
thing would just be like ball my eyes
out panic attacks at home but I told him
like like
I my my homie texts me like hey bro how
are you my response is I'm good man how
are you yeah you know what I mean like
it's like a wonderful opportunity yeah
and now it's like dude like my my
relationships with my friends are just
like like you know maybe we'll still go
we'll go grab a beer but we're going to
talk about this [__] and I'm just and
like we don't know what we're going to
say we don't know exactly the right
thing to say we don't know the there's
never right thing yeah you just you just
get it out and like the the the truth of
the matter is a lot of times it's like
when you just talk through these things
you learn that like your homie just
loves you man and they're like [__] man
that's okay I go through my [__] in the
same way sounds like you're going
through it that's all right bro what do
you need what do you you want to go for
a run you want to yeah like get out like
go for a drive whatever whatever it may
be uh just to get you out of the mindset
whether it be yeah I'm depressed and
stuff and then you may not realize that
you're social isolating and you have
somebody external
like my step sister went through some
stuff I went over there and I was like
no you're coming out she was like I'm
not coming out I just want to stay here
and kind of be in my own misery I'm like
Noom that ain't happening like yeah I'm
not going to let this happen yeah and so
I pulled her out her misery pit and took
her out to Willow that's where she
started kind of like breaking down to me
and crying and stuff I'm like that's
healing brother that's healing I mean I
I made sure to poke a little bit of fun
at her she's like oh what's wrong with
me I'm like well you kind of [__] up
eyebrows and a b big
head like just loving things and she's
like oh are you serious break yeah
breaks that tension just to be like no
nothing's wrong like if somebody can't
see that like you're a good person it
doesn't make you any less of a person
and people go through their own stuff
but it's the friends who are there to uh
really lift you up and take you out of
that hole are the ones that like I know
I did some really shitty stuff I think
last year to some people who were close
to me and I'm not proud of it and I've
owned up to it and stuff but uh I think
that you should definitely the people
who are there for you should definitely
cherish as good company yeah yeah dude
that that's so true I mean I like I feel
like over the last couple years I
because I really got just I was like
dude I got to focus on me like I've got
to just figure out what my mind's doing
I've got to like like why I hurting
myself why am I doing these things like
what I've got to [__] figure it out
and like I was afraid that um like like
the last few weeks I've been going
through some stuff in my personal life
it's just been really rough and I
haven't been as close the last couple
years with a lot of my homies MH and
it's just such a beautiful reminder that
that's okay like they still love me
because like as I'm going through it
like they're they're texting me like
what's up bro how are you today how are
you today like I'll get five different
people text me every day like just
checking in man how are you and like
there I was thinking that I I would just
put myself on this island and I'm like
[__] I haven't been a good friend like
crap I don't think I texted so and so on
their birthday last year like f [__] I'm
such a piece of [__] like I don't
deserve to have that that friend there
when I when I need help like blah blah
it's like no man it didn't like that no
and everybody has their different
language of love uh whether it's giving
gifts Time Communication touch or
whatever it may be uh just having that
open uh not like open relationship wise
but it's having that open source of
communication where you can go like a
year or so without seeing your friend
and then next time you see him it's not
like an a minute has passed and you're
like oh [__] man yeah like you remember
being on top of a Subaru sliding around
in the snow hanging out doing kind of
hood rat stuff and whatnot and yeah yeah
it's great yeah good people we're not
we're not measured by like how many days
in a row like dude like we're not a
[__] Snapchat streak bro where like
friendships are you know I have friends
who like you don't hear from them for 5
years and I guarantee like you just hit
him I mean look it if I haven't talked
to you for a while you come right over
and we're right into it man it's great
to see you it's I'm pumped to see you I
remember working at a plan Z and you're
like yeah man you can uh do pretty much
whatever the [__] you want here you can
I think it was I want to say verbatim
you're like yeah just don't smoke too
much weed where you people really notice
it if you're going to have sex do it in
the bathroom and other than that that
grip tape up and I'll see you in a while
oh [__] that's my management stuff yeah
I was like all right cool
dude that's so funny man yeah playc kop
that was awesome times yeah got wild at
the end though it always does was when
that guy was stealing a little
snowboards from of the pro shop and
selling it to us oh yeah and what the
[__] yeah I remember Jeremy was all
hopped up and like all stressed out and
I was sitting there watching Monty
Python's Holy Grail and he's like you
cool I'm cool are you cool I'm like yeah
dude I'm cool he's like okay just make
sure you're cool about this we're going
to have like the police raid this guy
and stuff I'm like yeah I'm cool and I
push play and then he started talking
like yeah dude I'm I'm solid like I'm
not stressed and the guy came in gave us
a whole bunch of boards and then got ran
sacked by the police out back and I was
like man [__] wild yeah I forgot about
that dude isn't that funny
like that's how it was too when I worked
at plan Z it was I mean because when
there wasn't customers in there I mean
that's the thing when you when you live
in a small town like some days are busy
and some days and and when you're
working you're working like so for me
it's like a customer comes in like
laptops closed they have my full
attention but sometimes it's like three
hours before someone comes in that's
just how it goes yeah that's actually
interestingly enough that's when I first
started learning how to like produce
like my I remember intro into dejing was
I remember that I remember I still have
uh all your music from your laptop at
that point saved on my uh external hard
drive that's epic because you're like I
was like hey man I know you got a ton of
music is it cool if like I just rip it
all into my external you're like yeah
[__] whatever and I'm like sweet I
copied it all over and put Jake's music
I haven't done that in a while but yeah
I got like your whole playlist to like
throw back to your whatever dang so yeah
there's some bangers on there it's so
crazy that that doesn't seem like it was
so I mean it seems like another lifetime
ago but I mean what 10 nine years ago
eight years ago something like that yeah
like that and then over at Mr Formal
working over there oh yeah work together
at Mr Formal yeah yeah that's phis and
Kip and Kip went down a different
lifestyle Kip went down a different
lifestyle yeah I mean I wish him the I
really hope Bandit he's prison is is he
in prison prison I mean I know I I heard
about all that I just didn't know like
what came of it like I want to say he's
in prisoned because yeah he he robbed
like a few Banks and Subways and
everything that is crazy dude he was
like one of the smartest [__]
like he very charismatic super I loved
him dude I thought he was awesome I
loved him only uh dispute me and him had
was he told me that lead singer of Fun
was better than Freddy Mercury like
better singer and everything I'm like
[__] no Freddy Mercury is the king
man Freddy Mercury is the king but I
will say the lead singer of Fun is so
good yeah he's a good singer so good
have you have you seen the one with him
and um Jana Jan Jan oh man I'm spacing
her name Jamie pull it up Jamie Jamie um
yeah no I think it's it's basically like
a live rendition of um tonight we are
young Whatever the song is okay with Jan
I was hoping I'd fall right into the
name again Jan and whatever I recognize
the first name Jana but I can't
recognize the last name I I know who
you're talking about but I just can't it
doesn't it's not clicking for me tip of
the tongue yeah yeah but I uh did you
watch the Freddy Mercury or or did you
watch the queen movie like yeah I I
watched it oh did you have negative
thoughts on it you don't like it no I I
thought it was good I I liked it I
didn't watch the Elton John one but I
like the Freddy Mercury one you got to
watch the Elton John one too it actually
is really good there's this scene I'm
just going to give it away right now
it's not going to break the movie or
anything there's a scene where like I
dude I got chill I think I was watching
on an airplane I got like chills
watching it it was just this cool
basically like it's not like a they
don't push the edge too much of like the
unrealistic stuff in the movie like it's
a pretty downto Earth movie but they do
have a couple parts that like show the
magic of Elton John and they had this
this scene they're they're in the club
and playing the piano and like they get
to this part of the song I don't know if
it was Saturday night or what it was but
um the boys his his he's like playing
and he's killing it and like his feet
lift up off the ground if I remember
correctly the whole room like
everybody's feet lifted up off the
ground and it was this cool I was like
wow what an interesting choice for the
director to take like I was just like
blown away and then like you know it
drops back into the course or whatever
it is they all down they're just jamming
and it was kind of like a subtle little
there isn't a bunch of magic in the
movie like that but they had that scene
and I was like this is one of the
greatest scenes that I've seen in a
movie it's so like it it'll stand out to
you now I'm sure but yeah it was worth a
watch it's it's a it's a lot about like
his personal bio but um the actor who
played Elton John fantastic yeah and
then uh Ramy Malik who played um Freddy
Mercury Freddy Mercury [__] killed it
killed it I thought I I'm not I haven't
been a huge Freddy Mercury fan like I I
haven't been like super overly obsessed
with Queen but I thought that he did a
fantastic job I mean I had their
greatest growing up I was like man these
are bangers Fat Bottom Girls uh all them
Killer Queen great and just the uh from
watching it I didn't know I didn't I
wasn't too keen on like what his life
was I knew like a little bit here and
there but I was like man there's a
there's a whole another Third Dimension
that like I just learned about this
person and it kind of came up uh it just
it's just cool learning about different
subjects and
uh like how he evolved as a
musician yeah I mean I I thought okay so
like when I excuse me when I grew up
listening to I liked Queen MH um it I
always thought it was kind of
interesting
after I feel like I should have liked
them more than I did I feel like they
were so original they were so pushing
boundaries at that time
but I feel like I would hear like like
Bohemian rap city I honestly didn't care
that much for the song I thought it was
ridiculous but it's weird because what I
like about a lot of other songs and a
lot of other artists is like that level
of like holy [__] you're allowed to do
that you're just doing whatever you want
on a track and it sounds like the
coolest like cuz music is not there's no
rules there's music theory cool but
there's not rules man you [__] if you
have anidea you want to put an opera
singer in the middle of your [__]
rock song like
what like that's the coolest thing ever
but it's weird because I never latched
on to Queen growing up yeah I I listened
to one of the big bands I grew up
listening to was a lot of funk like uh
Gap Band Love The Gap Band Gap Band I
don't think I know Gap Band uh Burn
Rubber on Me he dropped Burn Rubber
Dropped a Bomb on me it's kind of like a
they weren't really a well-known
band baby oh yeah I know that yeah g
band great uh know and I a lot of people
love the Beatles I just wasn't really a
big Beetle fan myself and I'll listen to
some of them now and they I almost say
they one of the first ones who had a
what type of album is that called
it's where you have a whole story like
Sergeant Peppers uh marching band dude
it's literally right the behind that
doors uh album right there is it behind
that doors's record right there um yeah
one of my other podcast guests brought
me actually the that album Sergeant
Peppers uh marching band yeah it's a
good album it's I think the Be Beatles
are great band uh I I always talked to
when I worked at the Chevron I talked to
Rachel about it and she was always
obsessed with the Beatles And I didn't
want to be like oh yeah Beatles are good
and stuff doesn't it doesn't it seem
like you have to be equally obsessed
with the Beatles yeah it seems some
people they bring so much energy into
the band and I love seeing the energy
100% I hate people who are dream
Breakers and stuff like they're just
trash to me like if somebody has a dream
no matter how ridiculous it is pursue it
like yes that's your happiness like I'm
all for it however ridiculous it is
um and same goes with bands like man I
would love to see this band I'm like go
do it like we're you should we're
short-lived like go enjoy it like if it
makes you happy or it brings a a single
drop of Serotonin don't let anybody like
stop you from doing something that you
love or you want to pursue as an
individual uh some of my friends
who like one of my really good friends I
haven't talked I talked to him recently
like recently being figuratively I want
to say was like back in February uh
Johnny Christopherson
uh I got a message from obviously a
scammer who spoofed his profile on
Facebook and messaged me he clicked on
the wrong ad or something it'll get you
it'll get you every time and he's like
oh hey how you been I'm like oh just
missed my favorite fruit fry Booter and
stuffz he's a rollerblade around if
remember him yeah and he's like oh okay
yeah cool and I'm like okay this isn't
Johnny like and so I started sending all
this like kind of vague stuff and at the
end I just sent him a whole bunch of
dickpics from like random people I found
on the internet and I screenshot the
whole conversation I sent it to actual
Johnny and he's like I miss you too blah
blah I miss your Chocolate Starfish and
stuff I'm like that's Johnny yeah and he
out doing his Boyer uh miss your
Chocolate Starfish that's the best
response [__] cuz I posted I sent that
guy a message like I miss your nipples
your suculent nipples Johnny do you miss
my Chocolate Starfish and he's like
honestly no and then he hit me the
scammer had the audacity to hit me with
one of the hardest lines I've read was
people change Connor you need to you
need to accept that fact and I'm like oh
[__] this this camer just laid it on
thick to me a scammer is like trying to
be adult like yeah he just laid it on
thick to me I was like God that hit me
hard in the heart that's when the dick
really really immature bro yeah that's
when the dick pic started sending and he
was like yeah man first thing he sent
was I do miss my nipples do miss your
Chocolate Starfish blah blah I'm like
that's Johnny I haven't talked to you in
a long time but like just full circle
back is like not talking to friends for
a while and instantly you can reconnect
like a second has a pass which is really
cool just like us um like good times I
think last time I ran to you was over at
the Chevron I think you're getting like
a bang or some sort of energy drink yep
and you were in like a rush to get
somewhere I was like oh yeah man how you
doing good good just good solid
conversation for however long that was
like 10 15 seconds and split ways sound
very long though that sounds sad no it
it time is relative uh yeah you can like
I said you can cherish the small moments
and like it's you don't have to have
like a full like 3-day hang out to
reconnect with somebody yeah because I
feel like uh yeah cuz I feel like I get
recharged by those like you know cuz we
have so much crazy [__] going on our
heads all the time and like I I feel
like when you I I distance myself from
social media and so I don't really like
people in my life I don't think about
them as often like like all the cool
amazing awesome people that I've met
that I'm like not been like best best
friends with but I'm friends with I
don't think about them as often anymore
now that now that I don't have social
media but when I run into them like run
into you I guarantee when I was walking
out I was probably like [__] dude I love
C [__] love see probably like your
energy just by like catching up really
quick getting a quick hug in like see
like how are you doing good like seeing
that you're doing good like you I walk
out of there and I'm just like man [__]
I love seeing that guy vice versa too I
was like that's my buddy Jake he's doing
great things really proud of him man
he's he's flying out to like Carolina to
go set up some thing from because he got
hooked up with uh with uh Deca to get
this sweet job flying now he's going
across the country making dreams come
true really proud of the guy he's
chasing his passions a that's sweet of
you man so I'll just like go on a
tangent for however long that is the
work day and by the end of the day
everybody else is all tired of me
talking about people I'm like okay yeah
I'll get back to work now clean up all
three yeah no that's the best thing man
I mean that's I mean that's like what is
this life in the end like we don't take
any of it with us we're that's what we
have is those interactions right you
know monetary stuff is all fleeting
looks are fleeting Beauty's a shortlived
tyrant tyrrany that's one of my favorite
quotes uh yeah beauty is a shortlived
tyrany or something like that one can't
remember who says that it's the same
it's not the same guy who says like a
thrown is a bench covered in in suede or
velvet I want to say that's Napoleon I'd
like that one too I don't know that I've
heard that yeah i' just get unless it's
the Iron Throne yeah from Game of
Thrones that's a good one very pointy a
lot of
tetanus a lot of dead people I've died
from those swords I'm sure
yeah yeah that's super
fun make can drink with my beer I will
do the
same what is the coolest job coolest job
that you've worked or even like coolest
place you've been to because of a job
even
um I've actually got pretty lucky with
my jobs I I loved working at plany just
people I worked with was super cool
you're hanging out with Cody Hooper all
day yeah Cody Hooper was great I love
Cody Hooper he's doing really good in
life I'm really proud of the guy
um the weed shop was really cool when I
work there I made like 220 bucks a day
just to sit there play Pokemon and smoke
weed wasn't bad I got smoking weed too
much I was smoking like an ounce a day
and like three to five grams of wax a
day Jesus Lord yeah I was burning
through my money I'd get like an ounce a
day and I'd smoke that all people like
oh man an ounce is a lot and I'm like
well if you roll it up into 28 joints
it's not that bad you just kind of puff
away yeah I mean do we get used to that
[__] I mean yeah builds up a tolerance
then
uh I worked on a cruise ship and lived
kind of over in Hawaii for a little bit
and that was kind of interesting kind of
sucked I'd work like 190 hours every two
weeks and I'd get paid like 800 bucks
yeah they screw you there pretty good
what' you do on the cruise ship I was
Hotel utility and and so I was in charge
of the Ford SS and spew crew and I met
some really really amazing people on
there who I still keep in contact I like
I really the only thing I like about
Facebook I'm a [__] poster I just post a
whole bunch of [__] I'm like oh it's
kind of funny share this share blah blah
and uh main thing I like about Facebook
and Snapchat I don't like the social
media aspect of it but I like being able
to stay in contact with people uh one of
my good friends Frank lives over on the
big Island still and every time I talk
to him he's like man uh when are you
going to quit your job and move over
here and do drilling with me I'm like
well I've got like $6,000 left in debt
and I might do that and blah blah and he
still hits me up about that and we
always catch up and talk and I always
put little not like bad ones but I put
Little Seeds of doubt in his mind of
like oh he probably shouldn't do this
he's like oh I got this
uh um this girl who like really likes me
and I'm like oh that sounds really good
just make sure she doesn't take you for
money stuff like oh is is she buying any
meals and stuff blah blah blah like just
poking fun out him yeah right right
right yeah I'm I'm always super stoked
to hear whenever anybody I meet doing
good in their life
uh and I think that's kind of gone the
way of the wind a lot of people want to
focus on themselves and kind of flaunt
their clout however it is whether they
got a new vehicle which is really good
to be happy like hey I got this new
vehicle and stuff but don't put other
people down like oh you wish you were
doing this and right right like yeah
it's like like brag about your
achievements and stuff and I'm all for
that but don't brag by putting other
people down like brag about building
yourself up um and I think that kind of
comes from today's mindset where you
have this competition on social media
which is why I don't like it where it's
like if somebody creates a business not
too many people are like super enthused
about it but if you get a job
everybody's super stoked about it it's
like you know Chase your passions do
what makes you feel good do what makes
you happy if you just if you posted that
you just ran like a five minute mile
hell yeah that's awesome cool I can't do
that like I'm not even gonna try saying
I can do that like I'm not gonna try
delegitimizing your happiness or your
accomplishment by even trying to compare
myself to that like you're doing great
in life there's nothing else I can say
like I wish I could do that I want to do
this take me out for some time take me
out to do this where I can share your
passion and share your enthusiasm which
is more so that's it's kind of a greedy
selfish thing to say that in a way in
that sense that I want to share your
happiness I want I want to do something
with you that makes you happy as an
individual whether it's a guy or girl
like this is something you're really
passionate about and you have drive for
it I want I want to dip my toes into it
see if it's something for me and share
this with you this moment or this
activity I may not it may not be for me
but it's the time spent and it's
the
uh the
overall um time together one of my
really good friends uh Danny we don't
really we talk a little bit here and
there
when I was really depressed and stuff
she's like hey let's go running I [__]
up and I didn't realize how much of a
runner she was and I saw that she was
like a she got college for like CR
country oh Danny's amazing are you
talking about Egon yeah great human love
her to death She's always positive um I
worked with her at warehouser actually
oh did you yeah she was yeah yeah she's
just a good human being I really
appreciate having her as a friend uh and
I [__] up I was like hey let let's go
running and so we went from our mom's
house down around the lake I thought
we're going to drive to the lake and
then run it and she's like oh it's only
like half a mile pretty much from the
house over there I had to stop so many
times I I felt blood in my lungs Vision
was blurring I was like Jesus coming to
take me like it's not good I'm gonna die
right here and she was not even huffing
a second even pass I was like God damn
like I [__] up she runs a lot she I
think she's always been longdistance
Runner yeah I'm a I'm a 10 yard Runner
and then I'm done for the day that's
that's my but that that is super cool
though I totally get what you're saying
is like this is I like to you know not
to like say a person is a portal and
just that but I mean if you consider
certain people are like portals to a
different world like it's like once you
get to know someone through friendship
and like you have certain things that
you or certain experiences that you've
had together um but then like there's
something that when they're really good
at it or they do it a lot or it's
something that they're passionate about
yeah that if you were just like you just
search like longdistance running on the
internet and you watch videos on YouTube
that is farfetched From A Distant
different that's a different thing than
actually experiencing it and doing you
know yeah I feel like friendships and
even acquaintances and even like it
doesn't have to be close friendships
like just all the people you meet it
really is like a portal into a different
world yeah but if you're a total
[__] or or you're not not a good
friend like you don't have those
opportunities you know what I mean like
that's dude that's why I feel like I I I
love the side of your personality you're
I feel like you're friends with
everybody in in a sense that like you
you are just genuinely inter interested
in people you're you are you you give
people the benefit of the doubt it seems
like no matter what like it's just like
yeah you're just a person and you're
awesome no I completely agree like I for
me I always try
if somebody doesn't like somebody I will
keep that in the back of my mind like
all right well you know little word of
warning and stuff and I'll give them the
benefit doubt some people don't want
them at the table and they don't want
them to eat and if I have a dispute with
somebody where we lose contact or
however you may want to say it just
because you don't sit my table I don't
want you to not eat it's just that you
know we go separate ways um I still want
you to do good in life and finding all
these different people with different
Outlets I love meeting new people I'm
really bad at creating friendships but
I'm good at making acquaintances more so
like I'll I'll make a good friendship
and like to me it seems like I don't
know if it's reciprocated on the other
end I'll be like hey like be and they
might be like they might have met me at
a different time in my life where I
might have been partying a lot and
always boozed up or whatever it may be
intoxicated in some Manner
and but once you
if if I have the opportunity to like
really hang out with you and be able to
send a message like hey let's
uh let's go floating or kaying or
shooting or something like that let's
let's do something or they're like no
I'm kind of feeling down or hey do you
want to do this I usually try my best to
be like yeah I'm not good at it so don't
expect me to be like going mountain
biking I I [__] up again and went
mountain biking with Cody shaver oh he's
an awesome person too I love Cody shaver
death he he's [__] awesome I've
always liked Cody lot yeah he is one of
the best human beings I've ever met uh
if somebody has an issue with him it's
more than likely Almost 100% that person
did something to him like he will go out
of his way to do something he'll take
the shirt off his back and I could see
that I could totally see that I don't
know him very well but my interactions
have always been [__] awesome with
that guy yeah he grew up like two houses
down from me and so he during that time
he wouldn't take Ibuprofen no drugs no
nothing and I would come roll down like
stoned out of my gourd and he wouldn't
judge me at all and I would just sit
there shoot the BS with him for a little
bit as he'd be dropping in like an
oversized rear end into some Prius he's
putting a giant [__] engine in a
geometra or something probably yeah some
ridiculous and I would just be amazed at
I'm always amazed at Cody schaer he's
always doing something very productive
and doing just cool stuff like it's not
for me but I'm Amazed by his knowledge
and his skill that he's put his passion
into like I I've called him up several
times been like hey man uh I don't know
what the [__] going on with my car and
he's like goes over there fidds around
with it for like 5 seconds and it run
like a top I'm like holy [__] dude like
that's the thing that's the portal into
like his his world yeah like he knows
that world so well but you were saying
you went mountain biking with him yeah
um like I used to ride bikes like you
know Just A to B nothing cool like BMX
or nothing I'm like hey I want to do
mountain biking and so he took me up
growler's
gch and I had a hard tail and he had a
full suspension he let me ride it later
on but he had this massive drop that was
probably like 80 feet drop just Steep
and I was just cussing the whole way
down just I couldn't [__] out a grease
BB my butthole was so tight just
stressed out and scared I was like oh my
God and he just flying through that
thing like a Gaz in the in the African
planes I was like man is impressive to
see like him on him doing something that
he is so good at and that's the thing it
always seems like Cody does something
for like three years and in that time
like he did uh Jess skis in that three
years he like mastered it he was doing
back flips going out do all these
competitions and I'm just like man
that's super impressive and I ran out to
him at Willow Grove he's like yeah I'm
going J ski and without hesitation like
you want to ride this I'm
like yeah I'm down I almost sunk it a
couple times and I'm waterboarding
myself and I was talking to uh I was
talking to Kelly because his brother's
super into jet skis too yeah yeah and I
was like man I'm out there and it has a
throttle on it and so I'm holding the
throttle and I get ripped off it and I'm
dragging myself through the cman slooh
uh the Columbia River and I'm just
getting drugg under water and I'd pull
up to get a breath there and then I'd
breathe in exhaust and I'd be like start
dragging again and then he'd go out
there and rip it around he didn't judge
he's like oh man come out again I'm like
let me toss you some gas money for like
the fuel that I burnt up for this 15
minutes he's like no don't worry about
it like just come out with me again
sometime and I'm like dude that is a
solid friend who just wants good for
people yeah he he just wants you like he
experiences something that brings him
joy and so of course he wants someone
else to experience it yeah that's that
portal man that's so cool he doesn't
judge just one of those good people who
no matter what I can be like oh [__]
Cody's just a Down to Earth
dude solid guy I would never ever in my
life say anything bad about him or I
mean it's just me like I don't like
talking bad about people even if they
really [__] me over uh I'll be like you
know things just weren't kosher between
me and this person whatever uh hope
they're doing good in life mhm uh but
I'm not going to I'm not going to
try making somebody I'm not going to try
bringing them to my side by talking [__]
about somebody I'm like you know it's
however it is it happened but it's yeah
it's like a waste of your time in a way
like was like like you can you can wish
them well it's it's like you could like
if if they if they did you wrong you
could even just be like yeah I just I
don't really ever think about them hope
they're doing well that's about it you
know it's it's like we do we like we get
caught up with wasting our own time like
talk you know gossiping and those sort
of things yeah dude you could be
spending your time doing so many other
cool things who was I want to say it's
like Teddy Roosevelt or something like
that was like smart PE dumb people talk
about other people and smart people talk
about their ideals yeah and like I mean
I had a falling out last year with some
friends and it was my own fault I
admitted to it I'm like hey my bad I was
a piece of [__] and stuff and what I did
was when I went to this party I saw them
there didn't treat them any differently
but I just didn't engage them and I was
I tried throwing out like the Olive
Branch to try smoothing things out and
kind of got shut down for that and so
when I was at the party I kind of made
it a point to have them open up
conversation with me and it never
happened I'm like okay well like I'm not
going to talk bad about you but if you
want to rekindle or anything like I I
tried throwing out the Olive Branch
first I'm going to have you
have the first step yeah in
rekindling it's kind of that that that
the ball's in your court now which
doesn't have to be like this is your
responsibility to talk to me now it's
like if you say hi boom I'll start
conversation and right go into it and
I'll be completely open and Converse and
stuff but I'm going to wait for them
to uh create the conversation and I've I
found some friends who are kind of like
two-faced where
they would talk crap about me behind my
back because one of my friends was over
at uh the go forth Festival back in like
2018 or something they're like oh uh is
when I was doing
the uh cruise ship over in Hawaii
they're like oh we told him it was a bad
idea he should never do it and my
friend's like no [__] you guys like he's
getting out of town he's doing something
he loves and it's what do you mean bad
idea like that's it's your life that
you're like it's not their life they're
not they're like no we told him it was a
bad idea completely and stuff blah blah
blah and my friend went up to bat for me
he's like no like I'm proud of him he
like he's he left Callis County he went
out lived in Hawaii for a while like
he's doing good uh he's chasing things
that make him happy and I was doing it
for my stcw to further my career in the
mar time industry and so I was using it
as a stepping stone more so once I got
that I was like I don't really care
about this job now that I got my
stcw and it just kind of was
disheartening to hear people who I
thought were close to me kind of talk
ill of my choices I'm like I know I made
some bad choices here and there but it's
life is never a simple yes or no where
you can continue on and be like well I'm
it I could go for a 30% APR or I could
go for like a 5% so like obviously if
it's like that everybody would have
their life made out and planned but life
never goes that way dude we're all just
desperately trying to figure it out like
I like I like I read this Reddit comment
um that it was just such great
perspective like this guy was basically
saying I follow a couple like advice
things and a couple things like on
trauma and a couple like um I don't know
this guy was basically just talking
about how he had to have this
conversation with this 14-year-old kid
MH and he said like he basically like
messed up um he said something wrong or
like him and his him and his kid gotten
an argument whatever and there was like
tension between him he tried talking to
him and basically what he said he went
into his son's room and was like dude I
I've never been a dad before I've never
this is my first time living I've never
lived a life before I'm trying to figure
it out just like you so you got to
communicate with me you got to if I say
I'm sorry you know like you got to we
got to talk about it whatever and I feel
like you know you you can't you got to
give everybody the benefit there's
certain levels where you don't just let
people walk on you of course there's all
those things of course but man I think
it's so so important to remember like
man that person didn't mean to hurt you
that person didn't they don't want to
feel sad they're not pumped that that
happened like this like wherever like
where my mistakes are in my life they
might not be in the same place that
other people's mistakes are yeah but
like if you're going to throw my
mistakes in my face like you got to you
got to take a glance of yourself like
what are your mistakes you know what I
mean and and you don't feel bad about
them it's just like you learn from them
and you got to move on you got to just
make yourself better and grow like we're
all just trying to figure this out man
yeah one of one of the best uh things of
life I learned I was over in uh Arizona
doing door Tod door uh Pest Control
sales and so they drop us off at like
7:00 or 8: in the morning and they'd
pick us up at 11:00 at night in Arizona
they drive us all around they wouldn't
bring us food or water and so Jesus yeah
I Dro brutal job yeah [__] sucked um I
dropped from like 180 pounds down to
like well I don't even know what I
officially dropped to but my buddy Quay
Nims picked me up I remember Quay dude
we used tocate back in the day I love
Quay he's such a good person I gave him
my brothers a crunch crch roll account
so he could log in unbeknownst to my
brother what's crunchy roll it's like an
anime website cuz me and him watch like
one piece and a whole bunch of other
stuff one piece is I is it on Netflix
now I think one yeah it is I love one
piece I've been watching it since 98
it's still going out every yeah new new
up chapter every week um and so I told
him I was like hey man shit's not going
good over here he's like if you can toss
me some gas money I'll come over and
pick you up on this date when I have the
day off took complete time out of his
life to drive from San Diego over to
Phoenix and back to pick me up solid
friend wow uh and when I got back over
there he was feeding me steaks eggs took
me out to King's Dominion just showed me
a really really good time his roommate
was hooking up with this girl and she
was like hey I got these free tickets to
AAL LaVine and Back Street Boys we have
two free tickets you want to go I'm like
yeah either I'm GNA sit in an apartment
Valiant combo dude it was a killer like
back stre boys kills it
I imagine dude they go in they've been
working for a while I was the only dude
like there was a whole bunch of chicks
my age sitting there dancing twerking
and stuff and I was one of the only
dudes there so they all just kind of
cluttered to me just seeing a dude I was
like I'm glad to be your totem pool like
be person I am yeah and uh after a week
of eating really good I weighed 125 lb I
was thin damn that's a lot of weight to
lose yeah and that was like a month and
a half just straight drop so what what
were you like doing you were like door
Todo sales trying of P control P control
yeah and so we were selling it for like
300 bucks and everybody else selling the
same product and everything else was 25
bucks and so it's really hard to get
sales what yeah wait why would you be
selling it for 300 is it they just they
had their uh te their tiers and
everything set up for like everywhere
else like up in the Pacific Northwest
but down in Arizona where like black
widows and scorpions are more prevalent
uh there's a lot more press control and
so they were doing the same uh same
exact product everything else just for a
lot cheaper 25 bucks and then like 50
bucks a month they come in sweep the
house spray the stuff and
done and when I was out walking one day
I was just bone thirsty they couple
times they'd give me like adol or
something to kind of like make you a
better salesman whatever Jesus yeah they
all preached to be Mormon and would go
out just doing a whole bunch of drugs
partying and all this stuff so they they
weren't ing what they preached and I was
just super dehydrated a couple times I
got like hallucinations from being so
dehydrated I was walking down some
Street I don't even know I think it was
like Gilbert maybe or
auki and I come up to this house and
there's this probably like 45y old black
guy and I'm like look man I'm not trying
to sell you anything at all I'm just
wondering if you have like a bottle of
water a cup of water or if you don't
want me having a cup of water if I can
drink from your hose just to get some
fluids in me he's like yeah man uh
there's some water bottles in the back
of my truck go and grab it I open up
this dude don't know who he is at all
open up his actual truck and go to reach
in he's like no no it's in the bed and
I'm like I'm sorry man did not mean to
ude on your some people would get pissed
like getting in my truck or whatever
yeah in this town I feel like people
pull a gun on you oh yeah and he's like
no no worries man we're all just people
trying to get by that's it and I'm like
dude thank you so much gave me a Bott of
water I'm like thanks so much anybody
else comes by just tell him to [__] off
like I appreciate it a lot like you just
people trying to get by though that's
the that stood out yeah that stood out
to me I was like man that's super cool
he was having a full on conversation
with like two other of his friends or
something in his garage let me grab a
bottle of water and just lay that on me
thick was like well there people just
trying to get by day to day and I was
like man thanks like that's it it
doesn't sound deep but like it it that's
moment you're dying of dehydration in
Arizona man I was like man thanks and it
would get from like it always saved like
98 up to like 114 and after like 110 it
just felt like breathing a hair dryer
yeah I was like man this
sucks yeah I like Arizona but it's super
hot that's so cool though that I I it's
funny how different things stand out at
different times in your life like do you
ever like do you ever kind of like look
at like you know maybe synchronicities
like [__] man maybe I needed to hear
that or maybe I needed to you know like
cuz now that's a you have that in your
mental toolbox now like that that story
rings around your head from time to time
you know yeah completely it it kind of
bounced back and like I'll i' I've said
that to a couple other people like when
I was fishing I'd come across people
Hess homeless and stuff and they had
this really killer deal up in at the
Safeway over by the three his mall for
like three cases of water for
$2.50 just a killer smoking deal for a
24 pack and so I load up my friend's Kia
Soul with it and I would bring a couple
bottles of with me on the boat when I
was working and any opportunity I saw a
guy homeless on the street or something
like that like hey man you thirsty he's
like yeah I'm dying of thirst out here
like here's three bottles of water like
and they would just like on borderline
break down I'm like dude we're all just
people like we're humans it's a human
aspect like I don't want to see you
struggling I'm not I won't probably give
you money just cuz I don't know where
it's going whether it's drugs whatever
your Vice might be or if you're actually
use it for food or water but here's some
actual water that can help you out yeah
and so I would just kind of and it was
kind of a selfish thing too because it
it brought a little serotonin and
dopamine to me being able to give good
and give back to people like hey I'm
doing good in life this is what I can
share it's not much but I got like six
cases of water in my back here's a
couple water bottles right dude I I
don't think that's I mean mean I don't
know if selfish is the right word I feel
like service is it's an underrated thing
man I mean I think that it's super okay
to feel good when you help someone yeah
I think that like when you because
basically like we get so used to like
trying to live our own lives like like
walking past like you can't live your
life and walk down and walk around in
Portland and like basically like you're
walking past so many homeless people if
you were really like stopping
interacting with every single one or
like your need like you'd be left with
nothing yourself like you wouldn't be
able to actually go about what you're
doing but when you do have a little
extra to give and you can give it's like
it's it's such a good thing I mean it's
like hey I'm helping you out and I'm
feeling good I mean it's we we get a
little muddy when it comes to social
media
posting um it starts to get like a
little weird like when people are
posting for social media but I think
that for it almost comes to like this
like being proud of yourself for like
bragging like
like like it's okay to be proud of
yourself hey I got a new car but when
you're saying like I got a new car you
[__] peasants can't get a new car
yeah look at this I got a beamer it's
like all right well you're going to have
a lot of problems with it but right yeah
so it's it's like like if you I don't
know you know like like CU I think it's
so easy to see say like a video of
someone like giving a homeless person
bottle of water like oh we out here
helping the homeless or whatever you see
like like the ironic thing on TV shows
and stuff but I I don't know though like
I mean like aren't we trying to set
examples for different people like
shouldn't we say like hey this is a cool
thing to do I'm like I think you know
what I think I think it's cool to be
proud of yourself for doing things that
help another one another person you know
like it makes me feel good like I don't
need to post myself on social media like
hey here here's a bottle of water like
I'm just like oh well give me those
Karma points yeah hit hit up that clout
but it it just it's nice to kind of give
back to whatever Community I'm in yeah
and if I'm if I'm doing good if my
friend has 40 if I have 40 bucks my
friend doesn't like let's go eat on my
dime no big deal money's money's
fleeting everything's fleeting you never
know you could be at the top of the top
of the bracket and next thing you know
you're dead broke and people are going
to remember when you're good to them or
even if it's not something monetary wise
like money food whatever it might be
like just time spent you're like oh [__]
hard times uh
come over hang out play some video games
play some drums whatever just spend time
and just get you out of whatever mindset
you might be in yeah that's super
important man I mean it's not everything
has to
be not everything has to be
transactional you know like all right
bro I'm giving you I'm giving you some
water so like later in life you got me
in water it's like no like it's it's an
unspoken it's like like we just care for
each other when we need it it's like
it's basically you know if you can see
when when you see someone in pain when
you see someone who's down on their luck
when you see someone who's just
not just assume that person probably
would love to have everything they've
ever wanted oh yeah they'd probably love
to like have a full meal right now like
a homeless person they would probably
like to have like a a house or they
probably like to have like at least like
a stable place to sleep or whatever but
like right now they don't they're just
down on their luck and so maybe it's not
the same version of like where you get
down on your luck or when you kind of
like po up your life a little bit or
you're you're not doing the right things
or whatever we all have different
versions of where we mess up but like in
the end we all just want love and we
want companionship and we want to just
like we just want to get by and like
live this life out you know like we
don't know where we're [__] going if
we're trying to populate other the other
places in the universe or whatever we're
doing yeah our own 20 cats yeah yeah
exactly um was do you think that was the
worst job that you ever worked was I
mean that sounds terrible what fishing
or what no uh uh in in Arizona the pest
control like um that was that seems
brutal it was really kind of shady I
didn't the job wasn't super bad um when
the last day came when I was really
working I had the owners of the company
come and kind of like try talking to me
and I already had my mindset I'm like
I'm not doing this anymore and uh they
were I was sitting there and I was
thinking of stuff I can do physically to
kind of show like on edge or something
and so I had like a little pocket knife
I was kind of flicking around and kind
of [__] fiddle [__] with and uh they
it was one of my buddies who got me into
it and they brought him up and they had
him standing outside the door listening
in and they had me they kind of the way
they worded the conversation kind of
make it seem like [__] him kind of and
that's some trickery [__] yeah they're
doing they're really good at trickery
and I was like they're like well can you
be friends with him andu I'm like you
know right now like I just I right now I
don't really want to be friends with
anybody wait so he was waiting out like
like you didn't know he was wait I had
no idea that he was waiting outside the
door so lame that's corny and they kind
of corned me into a spot where I was
like you know I don't want they kind of
agitated me at point I was like I don't
want to be friends with anybody right
now like I don't want to be with
anything and they're like all right well
so and so come in and he came in just
looking depressed I was like well [__]
you know like you just kind of backed me
into the corner with with a questioning
and words you
like I have the utmost respect for him
and stuff he's doing good in life he's
still doing that program uh hope he
continues to do good and stuff but like
just their business practices I wasn't
really a fan of they're trying to
emulate a big family type setting but
they would pit people against each other
and their whole business model wasn't
what I was led to when I joined in I was
like all right well it's kind of good to
know
and through all those experiences and
everything else have kind of held I mean
anything you do it's like stress in the
body you kind of hold on to a little
piece of it here and there and it
becomes as some people turn baggage uh
through life experiences you kind of get
that like oh well is there somebody
waiting out there or are they trying to
go me into something or are they trying
to get something for me or are they
trying to do something that benefits
them and stuff so it really makes it
hard to open up to people in a sense
where what what's the catch in this
where where do you benefit right and it
kind of goes back to your your core
group where you're like I know this
person from x amount of time I knew who
I know who they are as a person and I
know they don't want anything from me
as whatever sense it may be like I've
had people who've used me for money when
I've been down like I gave a person like
80 bucks one day when I was working on
the weed store I'm like man uh he's like
oh I got to pay a ticket I had talked to
this guy in years and I was friends with
his family really good and I'm like he's
I think he said like he had like 60
bucks I'm like okay no problem um well
here's 80 don't worry about getting it
back to me he's like well I I promise
I'll get it back to you tomorrow I'm
like okay man because I got a whole
bunch of bills I got to pay tomorrow so
I'm screwing myself on this and then
dude just took the money bought some
pills and dipped up to Seattle and
ghosted all my calls damn I've had
people
who have I've left stuff over at their
house like when I was smoking weed a lot
I left like a $400 bong and he tripped
over my hat that I left there and broke
my bong and I was like okay cool and I
was like well could you like give me
like 10 maybe 20 bucks for it you know
just no big deal like just a gesture
he's like no [__] that I'm going
partying down in Portland and he pulled
out like 320 bucks like cool so you're
gonna you're not willing to like kind of
help me out like from the product I lost
and you're gonna go party down Portland
kind of show and I remember one of our
mutual friends was like yeah he doesn't
see anybody else as an acquaintance
unless there's something he can benefit
from right and I was like well that's
kind of shitty
like uh you you shouldn't use people
for whatever yeah like stepping ston
yeah stepping stone for what you can do
and so there's always that little uh
little evil in the back of the head like
oh what's what's up with this how how
could they benefit from it and I've
always tried to kind of saave away from
it and be like all right well you know
uh I'm just going to give you the
benefit of the doubt until that like
until that bridge is burned MH uh I'll
leave it that but the thing is any River
can be re re bridged and so people
change in time I've had friends who were
on different drugs went down a really
bad path
path and others wouldn't really
associate with him or whatever the cause
might
be and I might have lost touch with him
for a little bit and I'll still give
them that benefit but then like I'll re
I won't usually like re reach out
but
the um the bridge can always be rebuilt
and with some of those friends I'm like
all right well you know things are in
the past it's water underneath the
bridge like we can move past it's no big
deal we're all human right things happen
we're human people make mistakes yeah uh
as we get older too like it's just like
you're going to make mistakes you're
going to trip up you're going to stumble
the thing is when you make a mistake
more than three times or however many
times it is it it quits becoming a
mistake and it becomes a choice MH and
some people are kind of blind to that
and they uh use it to their own
benefit where then you're like you know
this isn't healthy like in whatever
manner it may be
I'm going to sever ties for now and I
hope you do good I hope you regain get
back on your feet but at this point in
time I cannot associate with you yeah
from the choices you're making and I
still love you but I can't support what
you're doing and a lot of people have
that issue where they can't uh be open
like I'll say I love somebody like no
big deal I'll be like hey man I love you
man no problem and other people like
will kind of hesitate away from the word
it's like no it doesn't mean like I want
to have sex with you or nothing like
that it's like a term of endearment like
hey yeah I use I use love you all the
time man I'm I'm love you bro like I I
mean I'm I'm All About that like I want
to communicate like I see you you know
it's a term of endearment like some
girls uh will like if I'm being friendly
with them they're like oh he just wants
to [__] me it's like no like you're
super cool I don't want anything
physical or anything like Yeah I'm you
want to go fishing or something doesn't
mean I want to go like pipe you down to
the river or nothing I'm like hey let's
go fishing let's let's do this and I
understand a lot of girls have uh kind
of reserves and kind of hold back and
they're like oh what's the gain here and
it's like no it's like I don't like
bring your boyfriend whatever I don't
[__] care like I know you I don't
know him but bring him with like I'm
down to meet him and then it's kind of
being weird it's like no like meet us
down the river come floating with us see
that's I feel like that's the thing is
you always got to be able to give
someone the benefit of the doubt first
you have to open it up with the trust I
mean when they they prove that that you
that they're unaware of their mistakes
or that they're going to keep making
mistakes then you got to draw the line
you got to stand up for yourself but oh
yeah I feel like I feel like you you
could probably say that you've had more
like outside of those instances where
people have like screwed you over or
like tricked you like with waiting
outside the door like that's
weird like you can't is easy as it is to
stick to like those traumatic
experiences like those are enough to
where our brain is like [__] man now I
got like wait it's like am I mistrusting
everybody now like you can't let that
like grab you you know you got to like
as easy as it is to like bring that into
new relationships and stuff you got to
just like remember how many people
you've been able to call how many people
you've been able to trust you know like
and trust is a big thing yeah trust is a
huge thing it's just like in a
relationship yeah
like if I trust you and stuff I'm all
for it but once you break that trust
there's always at that point there's
always going to be a thing in the back
of the head like oh are they doing what
they're saying they're going to do or
what's going on and it just eats at you
like no matter if it's a friend or
something like well I trust I trusted
him and they burnt that trust Bridge
right and so no matter what at that
point on later on you're always going to
have that little seed of doubt in your
mind where you never know like you you
can care for somebody but you can't
trust them is kind of a difficult
thing where you want to see the best in
a person and see them grow as an
individual and uh grow
and um just do genuinely
good but like a small thing can really
ruin like one small gesture can ruin a
big thing right so yeah we're getting up
here in time my friend
you know what I want to you what I want
to talk about though the last subject
that I want to talk about is aliens
aliens all right I'm you think aliens
are real 100% what what form do you
think aliens are in like um or or do you
think they're going to present
themselves to us do you think we're
going to have interactions with aliens
in our lifetime what do you think I
think a I think aliens I'm 100% I
believe in aliens 100% I believe in
Sasquatch sasas um I believe in all kind
some maob stuff I think that well they
already had a Rel from the government
about UFOs recently yeah recently like
it's like like during during the coron
virus it's like hey we uncovered other
worldly vehicles and it was like from
the CIA or something it's like what what
like elaborate [__] like what
this changes everything kind of slip
that in and then uh they have like Venus
right now shows uh a chemical compound
that only a certain biome can make or El
it's in a lab yes
and I don't think that an alien has to
be like a gray or ET or something to be
alien it could be a simple microbi
microorganism where it's uh just a life
form it could be do I think that there
is
like other uh sentient beings of our
level are higher hell yeah the universe
is always expanding like the human mind
can't comprehend ever expanding it's
ever expanding like you can look into
the into the distance like we're talking
about about earlier everything big
everything small kind of the universe
you look out and there's more and more
and more to think that we're the only
planet just based off what our
circumstances are to create life with
hydrogen and everything there could be
like a energy base there could be
something completely different
uh oh nice bless me bless you uh yeah
there could be some outside our realm of
comprehension that's right I think yeah
like I I think it'll be
like like we I mean like I said we
understand things through our five
senses you know like that's what creates
like like if you believe in the theory
of Consciousness psychism is basically
like that's what like Consciousness is a
part of uh uh like like a combination of
of what this is like biology has
inherently all all these things combined
makes um Consciousness but so basically
if okay so so let's talk the the thing
that was on uh Venus mhm
like it could be the 400 million years
ago version like like like what what was
on Earth 400 million years ago could be
that exact same thing that's on Venus
now like so so maybe it's not like like
basically eventually if you put that
thing that's on Venus that that element
or whatever that whatever you put it in
like a hyperbolic Time Chamber you give
it 400,000 yeah hey you know and and you
give it a you give it some [__] years
like it'll form into something that's
like might be intelligent but yeah I
mean it could be like Mars gets sucked
up into the sun earth gets sucked up and
Venus gets drawn in close enough where
it condenses the atmosphere
down to like the primodial ooze and
stuff and then out of that that bacteria
it's just luck of the draw where enough
atoms or whatever connects into a
being and then it crawls out and then
couple Millennia later it's p
taxes then all a sudden we're like you
need a social security number yeah your
your number is xz1 122 yeah I think
that's uh Elon Musk child's name I think
so yeah some some close to that it's
like a I I want to say that he said you
you pronounce it Ash something yeah it's
a wild name I mean I mean we're like we
could name our kids whatever the [__] we
want like we don't have to name them
Bill and Jennifer I Ed and Fred yeah
yeah I'm all for weird names uh my
cousin a elementary teacher I think over
at Wallace and she has an Asian kid
whose name is Tarzan and I'm like that
is a badass name what a baller name yeah
she said that that's bold too like to
take that leap for his parents to just
be like yeah but that's cool [__] well I
guess in the their culture or something
it's um I probably sound really like
ignorant or something but it's a name of
power and so they chose a powerful
Western name and Tarzan was it and I'm
like that's super cool like I wish I was
named Tarzan yeah no that's a super
tight name I love it probably a wild kid
he probably he's going to have I think
that names decipher the person uh so
like you can find people with the same
names and find similar traits in them
and like you can find uh different
Connors and we all have kind of like
some sort of similar trait that's
defined by I don't know if it's like a
vocal thing where like you hear and
maybe it's the vibrations kind of
affects you and you're like oh that's
Connor and stuff and or that's Jake and
then you kind of have like in a sense a
predetermined Destiny of that name going
forward dude it could be I mean cuz we
are we're vibrational beings we're
controlled by frequency and vibration I
mean so yeah okay so think about even
like uh chance and stuff is like like
yeah it VI so so if you like if you get
into like chanting and M chanting and
that sort of thing you start to be able
to really notice where in your body is
kind of vibrating like
oh like if you do something like that
and you really just take the time to
feel in your body like is this my belly
like you can feel that way in your belly
you can feel that in your heart I mean
they do have it does have certain
meanings I
mean yeah that's interesting I don't
ever I don't I don't think about that
very often yeah cuz different names have
different uh things where they're like I
want to name my child something very
powerful in my culture and like in the
Muslim culture Muhammad is a very
popular name it's one of most common
names in the world I think so yeah
and like like you said coming from
wherever it is the vibrations come out
when you say it like in elementary or
whatever school you're saying that and
so it creates those vibrations in you so
it could affect the psyche in a manner
like and then having to say it like or
having your teach having your teacher
say oh you got to write your name a 100
times and you're thinking like Conor
Conor Connor con and you have those
vibrations going in you might just be
conspiracy theory but I think there's
some truth to it there's some [__]
something there that's yeah that's
interesting yeah because different parts
of your body like like your inner I I
listen to this guy who if you want to
talk conspiracy this guy he yeah that
too uh his name is Greg Braden and like
I've actually had like weird like
personal like spiritual experiences by
listening to his [__] I don't know if
it's coincidental or if it was just
different frequencies but he teaches a
lot of like a lot of it is so farfetched
that I'm like what the [__] but a lot of
it just seems to really just ring true
um and he was basically saying like
there's in our DNA or like in our
chromosones there is something between
us and apes that is that is massively
diff different in our um in that strain
and the thing that's different in humans
is the ability to like sing yeah so it's
not just like being able to talk but
it's the the ability to like sing sing
and it makes it to where so basically
we're given the gift of vibration
control in a sense right and so I I I
don't know I just wonder yeah people's
names could have a significant meaning
well it's kind of like pop music like
it's always the same uh arithmetic or
the same
uh concept or formula to create the pop
music or rap or anything it's those
beats and you can listen to like Mac
Miller to somebody way camera his name
who has the exact same beat and stuff
and it's the same beats that will like
kind of trigger whatever it is they
might have different words and stuff but
it's the same vibrations and it was a
popular song Back Then popular song now
and you hear it as when you're younger
is it freck Park Market the MC Miller
song um 100 grandkids is the one I was
thinking oh yeah oh that's off the good
Am album I like that album good am my
two favorite ones are circles and
swimming though and good swiming is so
good dude I love that song it shows his
growth as an artist really using
different instruments unconventional
instruments for hip-hop and stuff like
ipes and yeah more Orchestra related
like with the ThunderCats and his tiny
desk setting fantastic loved it I love
that I love that the tiny I feel like
I've watched that particular tiny desk
concert multiple times oh Thundercats
kills it and MC Miller he just it's a
completely you listen to his album beat
and stuff and it's a different pace and
you can really kind of tell the more
emotions in it and him just kind of
sitting there vibing and just feeling
the music kind of flow through him yeah
I feel like I just correlated when you
said Vib and I correlated that that to a
short term for vibration maybe that's
we're always trying to describe the vibe
the vibe is good the vibration is good
man yeah the vibe Good Vibes good energy
energy is a real thing goes back on
Aliens I think energy is a real thing
you can I trust my gut a lot more now
where you can you can hear somebody and
they might be leading you onto something
and your gut's like no no that ain't
right yeah and if you ever go against
your gut it turns out to be exactly what
your gut saying you're like no that
wasn't it and then it kind of slaps you
on the back of the head like I told you
yeah is that kind of weird where like
it's always so hard because you're
you're always battling between it you're
like I don't know like what I know
what's true I know what's right I what's
like in my gut and then like the thing
is is like later on like if you feel
like guilt or shame or something it's
like a [__] I should have listen to my
gut you know yeah like it's like signal
that's that Vibe well it's a Vibe Conor
speaking of Vibes you're good vibes man
I'm pumped that you came over I I love
to just like it was it's super great to
just shoot this [__] you know always a
pleasure with you man yeah dude I like I
I I originally had wanted you to come
over cuz I was just like Conor is just
when it comes to talking to interesting
people Connor's always
just I feel like I'm always just
listening when you're talking like I'm
just like I'm just enthralled you know
like I feel like you're you're a good
Storyteller because you're just truthful
and you're just talking about your life
I feel like you're always positive uh I
don't know man I I I had a great
conversation and I appreciate you coming
here every time I've had an encounter
with you whether brief or elongated it's
always been a good time uh cherish every
moment and whether they be fleeting I'm
I'm always proud of seeing what you're
doing in life and just always exceeding
and pushing
envelope uh in your own personal life
and professional life it's good seeing
you do what you love to do so I've thank
you brother I enjoy just enjoy this man
I do too yeah hug from across the table
yeah yeah thank you bro all right
listeners take care of yourself hit up
Connor if you need a friend and drink
some [__] water if you haven't drank
any water today what are you doing drink
some water take care of yourself stay
hydrated stay high hydrated have better
conversations with
[Music]
ourselves knowledge is
power reality is
[Music]